<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vulnerability Scanners on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/</link><description>Recent content in Vulnerability Scanners on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 10:24:25 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Manage Pre-Installed Scanners</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/manage-pre-installed-scanners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/manage-pre-installed-scanners/</guid><description>Manage Pre-Installed Scanners You can find pre-installed vulnerability scanners under Administration -&amp;gt; Interrogation Services -&amp;gt; Scanners. If you click on an arrow next to a scanner, you&amp;rsquo;ll see the most important details about it. If you select a scanner using the small circle next to its name, you can perform the following actions with it
Set a Default Vulnerability Scanner Use the Set as Default button to set a new default scanner for your instance: Edit Existing Scanner Click on the Action button and then select Edit: That will open a dialogue window where you can change:</description></item><item><title>Add New Scanners</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/add-new-scanners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/add-new-scanners/</guid><description>Add New Scanners Although vulnerability scanning is a highly unified procedure, different scanners may capture different vulnerabilities. Some scanners are developed to act in a more severe way than others to meet specific compliance requirements. Nonetheless, adding more scanners may increase the general coverage and improve your cyber security.
To add a new scanner:
Expand Administration; Go to Interrogation Services; On the Scanners tab, click + New Scanner; Fill in the form: Give your scanner a name; Optionally, add a description; Enter the endpoint URL or IP address (if you are using an internal server); Choose your authorization method: For Basic one, enter your username and password which you received from the scanner provider; For Bearer, enter the secret token from your provider; For API key, enter the API key from your account on the scanner service provider.</description></item><item><title>Scanning Artifacts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/scanning-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/scanning-artifacts/</guid><description>Scanning Artifacts Read more about vulnerability scanning and how the health score is calculated here.
Running a System-Wide Scan As a system administrator, you can scan all artifacts in your instance at once.
Go to Administration; Click Interrogation Services; Select Vulnerability tab; Click Scan now. This will set the whole process in motion. You can watch the progress. Schedule a Scan Inside the vulnerability tab, you can schedule a system-wide scan.</description></item><item><title>General Configurations</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/general-configurations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/general-configurations/</guid><description>General Configurations System-Wide CVE Allowlist You can manage your deployment security by excluding certain vulnerabilities – entries in the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures List – from the health score calculation. Project admins can do this on the project level re-using system-wide CVE lists or creating their own.
Add Items to a System-Wide CVE Allowlist In the navigation pane, expand Administration; Go to Configuration; Open System Settings; Scroll down to Deployment Security; Click ADD; Find the vulnerability in this database; Enter the items separated by simple commans or line breaks; Select an expiration date for the allowlist or click Never expires; Click ADD; Click Save.</description></item></channel></rss>