<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/</link><description>Recent content in Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Database Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/database-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/database-authentication/</guid><description>Database Authentication The database user authnetication mode is applied by default. With this mode, all user management happens in the Container Registry GUI and the data is stored in the local database.
When selecting this authentication mode, keep in mind that once you added any users (except for yourself) to the instance using the database mode, the instance will be locked from switching to any other mode.
Nonetheless, this mode has a few advantages.</description></item><item><title>Preheat Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/preheat-images/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/preheat-images/</guid><description>Preheat Images: P2P Preheat Policies Introduction to P2P Preheat: How It Works Peer-to-peer (or P2P) networks are file sharing systems that do not involve a server. A peer is a computer in such a network. A seeder provides files for a leecher. The seeder uploads and the leecher downloads them. These two operations happen simulteneously, and the files go directly from one peer to the other.
Although there is no server, there is a managing software that coordinates uploads and downloads and keeps a record of which files are available for download and from which seeder.</description></item><item><title>Robot Accounts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/robot-accounts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/robot-accounts/</guid><description>Robot Accounts Robot accounts are used to access your project through an API. They perform a limited range of actions that you can specify per account and are generally used for workflow, deployment, and testing automation. Robot accounts can access only one project. They cannot be transferred to other projects.
Overview of Existing Robot Accounts Inside a project, under the Robot Accounts tab, you will find a list of the robot accounts associated with the project.</description></item><item><title>Repositories</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/repositories/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/repositories/</guid><description>Repositories Repositories can be described as folders within one project. If a project is a storage for images involved in the same application, the repositories can be a method to sort these images depending on the application feature, stage in the development life cycle, or any other factor.
Browse and Filter Repositories Inside every project, you will see the list of all its repositories. Similarly to filtering and searching through projects, you can use a search field to find a repository by its name:</description></item><item><title>Prerequisites</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/prerequisites/</guid><description>Prerequisites The only prerequisite for you is to install Docker. Check the system and hardware requirements for Docker in its official documentation and follow the instructions to get it running on your machine.</description></item><item><title>Why Use Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/why-use-container-registry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/why-use-container-registry/</guid><description>Why Use Container Registry as a Service Container registries are storages for your container images. It is a great supplementary service for containerization technology that saves you a lot of headaches when you run Kubernetes clusters to test and deploy your containerized applications.
Why Use a Container Registry When you work with Kubernetes deployments, you face the chicken-egg dilemma: you cannot keep the images in the cluster but you need them to run it.</description></item><item><title>Register at Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/register-at-container-registry/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/register-at-container-registry/</guid><description>Registration for System Admins All accounts with a Dedicated Service subscription can have multiple users. For the first time, the system administrator must complete the subscription purchase and configure the instance to enable other users to work with it later.
Users of Individual accounts are considered system admins of their accounts. The registration is the same.
To start working with Container Registry:
Go to our pricing page; Select your subscription or start a free trial; Fill in the form and provide your credit card details; Check your emails: you must have received a confirmation that your account has been created; Inside the email, click on password to display your password; you will be re-directed to a single use secure URL generated by OneTimeSecret where you can see your password for the Container Registry account; NOTE</description></item><item><title>UAA Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/uaa-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/uaa-authentication/</guid><description>UAA Authentication A user authentication and authorization server issues access tokens for your application to make it able to access another application: in this case, your Container Registry instance. You can configure a UAA server by yourself or select a provider that will set up for you a UAA instance. This instance will generate a token every time the user identity was confirmed – the user was authenticated – to enable user authorization that allows the user to perform certain actions in the system he was successfully logged in to.</description></item><item><title>Push and Pull Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/push-and-pull-images/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/push-and-pull-images/</guid><description>Push and Pull Images Pushing and pulling images is explained in detail in this getting started guide.</description></item><item><title>Tag Retention</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-retention/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-retention/</guid><description>Tag Retention Instead of deleting tags manually, you can set when they should &amp;ldquo;expire&amp;rdquo; by defining the tag retention.
WARNING
Once you set a retention rule, the artifacts that are not covered by it, will be deleted.
However, the operation is conducted at the artifact level. Artifacts that have more than one tag will be retained even if not all their tags are covered by the retention policy.
Create a New Tag Retention Policy Inside a project, go to the Policy tab (1); Switch to TAG RETENTION (2); Click ADD RULE (3); A dialogue window will appear:</description></item><item><title>Artifact Page</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/artifact-page/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/artifact-page/</guid><description>Artifact Page When you click on a single artifact, you will be redirected to a view showing detailed information about this artifact. In this view, you can also perform a few additional actions on the selected artifact.
Tags Overview Working with tags is described in detail in another tutorial since the features for doing this are distributed across the GUI. The current section explains general GUI features that are available in the single artifact view.</description></item><item><title>Managing Project Users</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/managing-project-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/managing-project-users/</guid><description>Managing Project Users The user that created a project and the super admin of the instance can add users to projects to enable them to perform different actions. As we mentioned in the previous article,
it is possible to pull images from a public repository without being a project member. But a membership grants users other rights depending on the role they are assigned.
Project Member Permissions Below is the overview of all project permissions by five types of roles:</description></item><item><title>Register in Your Instance</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/register-in-your-instance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/register-in-your-instance/</guid><description>Register in Your Instance Container Registry is a cloud-based solution that you can use in your browser.
Your Instance on Container Registry All accounts wuth a Dedicated Service subscription receive a subdomain on container-registry.com. Your organization can also request a custom domain.
Every subdomain/domain represents one instance. For different instances, you need different login credentials.
Registration Methods As a user, you can use one of these methods to register in your Container Registry instance:</description></item><item><title>What Is Harbor?</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/what-is-harbor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/what-is-harbor/</guid><description>What Is Harbor? Our service is built upon Harbor. Harbor is an open-source technology for storing and managing container images. It was developed by VMware, a leading provider of virtual machines, and then transferred to the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), one of the biggest open-source initiatives.
In its turn, the Harbor project evolved out of Docker&amp;rsquo;s source code. Its contributors attempted to enhance the latter and eliminate its security problems.</description></item><item><title>LDAP/AD authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/ldap/ad-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/ldap/ad-authentication/</guid><description>LDAP/AD authentication Every company needs a directory where all user login data is kept. There are two popular technologies for configuring and managing such directories – Windows Active Directory (AD) and Lightweight Directory Access Protocol – that are Harbor-compatible. It means that you can use an LDAP/AD server to add new users to the Container Registry instance and manage existing accounts.
Indeed, you need to set up and configure such a server before you can activate this kind of user authentication in Container Registry.</description></item><item><title>Tag Immutability</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-immutability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-immutability/</guid><description>Tag Immutability What Is Tag Immutability and Why You Need It Harbor, the technology behind Container Registry, cannot (yet) deal with the situation when more than one image has the same tag. When there is an image in the registry with a certain tag, and then another image with the same tag is pushed to it, the first image loses its tag. The second image, pushed later, retains the tag but only until the next image with the same tag is pushed.</description></item><item><title>Working With Tags</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/working-with-tags/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/working-with-tags/</guid><description>Working With Tags Image tags have a function to those of the branch refs in Git: pointing to a state of the artifact at a specific time. Originally, the purpose of image tags was to differentiate between multiple versions of the same image. But more often than not different tags may refer to the same image.
The tags come in handy when you want to pull and run an image. SHA256 hashes – the native identifiers of the Docker images and their versions – are difficult to read and impossible to memorize.</description></item><item><title>Push and Pull Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/push-and-pull-images/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/push-and-pull-images/</guid><description>Push and Pull Images Push Images: Steps Log In to Docker You need to log in to Docker to push and pull images to and from Container Registry. For this, you can use your Container Registry username but you need to generate your CLI login for Docker first.
Go to your user profile in the upper right corner of the cockpit: Copy the CLI secret: In your command line tool, log in to Docker: docker login your-subdomain.</description></item><item><title>Container Registry User Interface: A Short Overview</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/container-registry-user-interface-a-short-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/container-registry-user-interface-a-short-overview/</guid><description>Container Registry User Interface: A Short Overview When you log in to your Container Registry account as a user, you will see the following console.
NOTE
If you log in as an administrator, you will see an additional administration section. Refer to our Administration Guide for the GUI features overview.
Main GUI Features The navigation pane provides you access to your projects and logs.
Projects are folders for your images which can be assigned certain settings.</description></item><item><title>Webhooks</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/webhooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/webhooks/</guid><description>Webhooks Webhooks are API push notifications sent in the form of HTTP or HHTPS POST requests. They pro-actively deliver messages to other applications when some event occurs inside their own application.
They can inform or trigger further events in the destination application. For instance, you can directly deploy an application upon the image push. This allows you to automate your deployments.
In Container Registry, you can add either an HTTP or Slack-based HTTPS URL that will be used for receiving the messages by the target application.</description></item><item><title>Other Useful Features</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/other-useful-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/other-useful-features/</guid><description>Other Useful Features Our Harbor-based cloud service allows you to manage your images easier. Apart from pulling and pushing images to and from your container registry, you can:
Facilitate your Kubernetes deployments by seamless integration between your Kubernetes clusters and Harbor-based container registries; using Kubernetes YAML manifests: Helm Charts; access your Chart Museum directly from the GUI Bypass connectivity issues by using a proxy cache: a pull-through cache for another target registry; a cached copy is checked against the target and is always up-to-date.</description></item><item><title>Working With Logs</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/working-with-logs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/working-with-logs/</guid><description>Working With Logs Logs track everything that happens in your system. You can access logs from different places in the GUI.
Event Logs You will see this side bar on the right from everywhere in Container Registry. Hover over the EVENT LOG tab to exapnd it.
Event log includes high-level events, for instance, adding or deleting a new user to the system:
In some cases, project-related events will be also displayed in this section.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Individual Account</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/dedicated-vs-individual-account/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/dedicated-vs-individual-account/</guid><description>Dedicated vs Individual Account Container Registry offers three types of accounts:
individual; dedicated; custom/enterprise. The present documentation is mostly written with dedicated accounts in mind. We would like to explain the differences between the three. The table below summarizes critical distinctions. You can also refer to our pricing page.
Position Individual Dedicated Custom Tenants 1 tenant Multitenancy Multitenancy Repositores Only private Private and public Private and public Domain c8n.</description></item><item><title>Double-Starred Patterns</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/double-starred-patterns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/double-starred-patterns/</guid><description>Double-Starred Patterns Some of the Container Registry GUI features allow you to use string matching instead of entering complete names of repositories or tags. That comes in handy if you create separate repositories or tags for every stage in the software development lifecycle and follow a naming convention. In this case, you can select more than one repository or tag by typing in only the pattern once instead of listing all their names.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/getting-started-with-harbor-container-registry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/getting-started-with-harbor-container-registry/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ready to push the image to a registry? In this post, we will discuss how to get started with Container Registry.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Harbor Release 2.2.0</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/harbor-2.2.0-new-features-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/harbor-2.2.0-new-features-explained/</guid><description>&lt;p>Harbor 2.2.0 was just released and comes with some very interesting features.
This post walks you through the newly added features and changes explaining the capabilities. Since the last release of v2.1.0 in September 2020, eleven contributors made 41 changes and resolved 189 issues.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Subscription Success</title><link>https://container-registry.com/subscription/success/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/subscription/success/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s Next? As you can see, we already started the setup process and within a few minutes, you will receive:
A welcome email with the URL and credentials to your new container registry Order confirmation email from our subscription management system While you ar waiting In the meantime, you can check out the following resources:
Blog Frequently Asked Questions Improve your containerized workflow Help Support Chat is the best way to contact us for real-time support and technical problems.</description></item><item><title>Distributing Commercial Software Through Container Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/distributing-commercial-software-through-container-images/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/distributing-commercial-software-through-container-images/</guid><description>&lt;p>When delivering software to clients, many independent software vendors (ISVs) still rely on methods involving traditional software packaging methods such as downloadable binaries, ZIPs, or other type of compressed delivery. These distribution approaches are often OS specific. As a result, developers are forced to spend precious time on tailoring software delivery rather than innovation. Containerization is already simplifying software delivery for many of today&amp;rsquo;s mainstream products. Choosing the right &lt;a href="https://container-registry.com">container registry that meets ISVs requirements&lt;/a> is crucial to satisfy vendors and meet client expectations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifting Developers’ Productivity with BuildKit CLI for kubectl</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/productivity-lift-buildkit-cli-for-kubectl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/productivity-lift-buildkit-cli-for-kubectl/</guid><description>&lt;p>Developing and testing software on Kubernetes usually means building and moving container images from the developer workstation to a container registry, and ultimately, Kubernetes. When considering all the moving parts, the complexity and context switches break the development flow. Gone are the days where developers just hit a command and a few seconds later the newly built software is ready for testing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What if there was some magical tool that you could simply feed instructions like: &amp;ldquo;Build this Dockerfile &lt;em>here&lt;/em> and replace any existing image on &lt;em>that&lt;/em> Kubernetes cluster with the results!&amp;rdquo; ASAP. Spoiler Alert! That is exactly what BuildKit CLI for kubectl is there to do.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>3 Ways to overcome the Docker Hub pull rate limit</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</guid><description>&lt;p>As someone who is working with Docker Container images, you came across the new Docker Hub pull rate limit or perhaps you are already here because you encountered the error message &lt;code>You have reached your pull rate limit&lt;/code> and are now looking for a solution on how to resolve it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Container Registry Terms of Service</title><link>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</guid><description>Container Registry Terms of Service Effective as of: November 1, 2020
These Container Registry Terms of Service (these &amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) apply to the features and functions provided by 8gears Ltd.(&amp;ldquo;8gears,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) via container-registry.com, private-docker-registry.com, c8n.io and c8n.me (the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;, collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;).
By accessing or using the Services, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, do not use any of the Services.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://container-registry.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/about/</guid><description>Container Registry started out in 2016 as a Portus Powered Container Registry Service for teams and organizations. In September 2020 we switched the software stack to Harbor as the new foundation to better support cloud native and multi cloud workloads.
Our Background Many solutions arise from their own and immediate needs. We were building a new microservice-based software stack for a new project and faced for the second time in a row the difficulty to find a decent Docker Registry suitable for teams and organizations.</description></item><item><title>Containerized Software Distribution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/containerized-software-distribution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/containerized-software-distribution/</guid><description>Distributing Commercial Software Through Container Images Distribute your software as a Docker Container. Give your customers a straightforward way to use your Containerized Software. Manage and automate customer access as wells as the access duration to container images. Link container images access to paid subscription plan. The possibilities are endless.
Offer Safe and secure Dedicated Container Registry Your branding with a custom domain Not Yet Convinced? Write us, chat with us or give us a call for an individual consultation.</description></item><item><title>Improve your containerized workflow</title><link>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</guid><description>Improve Your Containerized Workflow Register for a free and individual session with an expert on how to improve your containerized workflow.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy of Container Registry Effective as of: November 1, 2020
Container Registry collects some Personal Data from its Users.
This document can be printed for reference by using the print command in the settings of any browser.
Our Privacy Policy at a Glance This is a condensed overview of the Personal Data we collect for the following purposes and using the following services:
Owner and Data Controller 8gears Ltd.</description></item></channel></rss>