<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/</link><description>Recent content in Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 Ways to overcome the Docker Hub pull rate limit</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</guid><description>&lt;p>As someone who is working with Docker Container images, you came across the new Docker Hub pull rate limit or perhaps you are already here because you encountered the error message &lt;code>You have reached your pull rate limit&lt;/code> and are now looking for a solution on how to resolve it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Container Registry Terms of Service</title><link>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</guid><description>Container Registry Terms of Service Effective as of: November 1, 2020
These Container Registry Terms of Service (these &amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) apply to the features and functions provided by 8gears Ltd.(&amp;ldquo;8gears,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) via container-registry.com, private-docker-registry.com, c8n.io and c8n.me (the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;, collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;).
By accessing or using the Services, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, do not use any of the Services.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://container-registry.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/about/</guid><description>Container Registry started out in 2016 as a Portus Powered Container Registry Service for teams and organizations. In September 2020 we switched our foundation from Portus to Harbor, to better serve those that mean the most to us, our customers.
Background Many solutions arise from their own and immediate needs. After we started a new container-centric consulting project and faced difficulties to find a decent alternative Docker Registry for the organization we were building, we merged into a microservice-based software.</description></item><item><title>Improve your containerized workflow</title><link>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy of Container Registry Effective as of: November 1, 2020
Container Registry collects some Personal Data from its Users.
This document can be printed for reference by using the print command in the settings of any browser.
Our Privacy Policy at a Glance This is a condensed overview of the Personal Data we collect for the following purposes and using the following services:
Owner and Data Controller 8gears Ltd.</description></item></channel></rss>