<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/</link><description>Recent content in Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>OIDC configuration for Google Workspaces</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-guide/oidc-configuration-for-google-workspaces/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-guide/oidc-configuration-for-google-workspaces/</guid><description>How to Setup Google Workspace as OIDC Provider for Your Harbor Container Registry In this tutorial, we will show you how to configure all necessary settings in your Google Workspace.
The steps appear in chronological order but some of them may be skipped if you already dealt with Google Cloud before.
The other tutorial explains what you should do in your Container Registry instance if you want to use OIDC authentication in general.</description></item><item><title>Why Use Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/why-use-container-registry/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/why-use-container-registry/</guid><description>Why Use Container Registry as a Service Container registries are storages for your container images. It is an essential service for containerization technology that saves you a lot of headaches when you run Kubernetes clusters to test and deploy your containerized applications.
Why Use a Container Registry When you work with Kubernetes deployments, you face the chicken-egg dilemma: you cannot keep the images in the cluster but you need them to run it.</description></item><item><title>Database Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/database-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/database-authentication/</guid><description>Database Authentication The database user authnetication mode is applied by default. With this mode, all user management happens in the Container Registry GUI and the data is stored in the local database.
When selecting this authentication mode, keep in mind that once you added any users (except for yourself) to the instance using the database mode, the instance will be locked from switching to any other mode.
Nonetheless, this mode has a few advantages.</description></item><item><title>Robot Accounts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/robot-accounts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/robot-accounts/</guid><description>Robot Accounts Robot accounts are used to access your project through an API. They perform a limited range of actions that you can specify per account and are generally used for workflow, deployment, and testing automation. Robot accounts created on the project level can access only one project. They cannot be transferred to other projects.
To create robots that have access to multiple projects, create system robot accounts as explained here.</description></item><item><title>Repositories</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/repositories/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/repositories/</guid><description>Repositories Repositories can be described as folders within one project. If a project is a storage for images involved in the same application, the repositories can be a method to sort these images depending on the application feature, stage in the development life cycle, or any other factor.
Browse and Filter Repositories Inside every project, you will see the list of all its repositories. Similarly to filtering and searching through projects, you can use a search field to find a repository by its name:</description></item><item><title>Prerequisites</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/prerequisites/</guid><description>Prerequisites The only prerequisite for you to get started is to use an OCI compliant container runtime environment, such as Docker or Podman.
Check the system and hardware requirements for Docker in its official documentation and follow the instructions to get it running on your machine. You can refer to the respective install guide for Podman.</description></item><item><title>Access</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/access/</guid><description>Access Properties Name Type Description Notes resource str The resource of the access [optional] action str The action of the access [optional] effect str The effect of the access [optional]</description></item><item><title>Accessory</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/accessory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/accessory/</guid><description>Accessory Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the accessory [optional] artifact_id int The artifact id of the accessory [optional] subject_artifact_id int The subject artifact id of the accessory [optional] size int The artifact size of the accessory [optional] digest str The artifact digest of the accessory [optional] type str The artifact size of the accessory [optional] icon str The icon of the accessory [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the accessory [optional]</description></item><item><title>ActionRequest</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/actionrequest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/actionrequest/</guid><description>ActionRequest Properties Name Type Description Notes action str The action of the request, should be stop, pause or resume [optional]</description></item><item><title>AdditionLink</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/additionlink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/additionlink/</guid><description>AdditionLink Properties Name Type Description Notes href str The link of the addition [optional] absolute bool Determine whether the link is an absolute URL or not [optional]</description></item><item><title>AdditionLinks</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/additionlinks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/additionlinks/</guid><description>AdditionLinks Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>Annotations</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/annotations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/annotations/</guid><description>Annotations Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>Artifact</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/artifact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/artifact/</guid><description>Artifact Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the artifact [optional] type str The type of the artifact, e.g. image, chart, etc [optional] media_type str The media type of the artifact [optional] manifest_media_type str The manifest media type of the artifact [optional] project_id int The ID of the project that the artifact belongs to [optional] repository_id int The ID of the repository that the artifact belongs to [optional] digest str The digest of the artifact [optional] size int The size of the artifact [optional] icon str The digest of the icon [optional] push_time datetime The push time of the artifact [optional] pull_time datetime The latest pull time of the artifact [optional] extra_attrs ExtraAttrs [optional] annotations Annotations [optional] references list[Reference] [optional] tags list[Tag] [optional] addition_links AdditionLinks [optional] labels list[Label] [optional] scan_overview ScanOverview The overview of the scan result.</description></item><item><title>AuditLog</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/auditlog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/auditlog/</guid><description>AuditLog Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the audit log entry. [optional] username str Username of the user in this log entry. [optional] resource str Name of the repository in this log entry. [optional] resource_type str Tag of the repository in this log entry. [optional] operation str The operation against the repository in this log entry. [optional] op_time datetime The time when this operation is triggered. [optional]</description></item><item><title>AuthproxySetting</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/authproxysetting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/authproxysetting/</guid><description>AuthproxySetting Properties Name Type Description Notes endpoint str The fully qualified URI of login endpoint of authproxy, such as 'https://192.168.1.2:8443/login' [optional] tokenreivew_endpoint str The fully qualified URI of token review endpoint of authproxy, such as 'https://192.168.1.2:8443/tokenreview' [optional] skip_search bool The flag to determine whether Harbor can skip search the user/group when adding him as a member. [optional] verify_cert bool The flag to determine whether Harbor should verify the certificate when connecting to the auth proxy.</description></item><item><title>Body</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/body/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/body/</guid><description>Body Properties Name Type Description Notes dry_run bool [optional]</description></item><item><title>Body1</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/body1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/body1/</guid><description>Body1 Properties Name Type Description Notes action str [optional]</description></item><item><title>BoolConfigItem</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/boolconfigitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/boolconfigitem/</guid><description>BoolConfigItem Properties Name Type Description Notes value bool The boolean value of current config item [optional] editable bool The configure item can be updated or not [optional]</description></item><item><title>ChartMetadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/chartmetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/chartmetadata/</guid><description>ChartMetadata Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The name of the chart home str The URL to the relevant project page [optional] sources list[str] The URL to the source code of chart [optional] version str A SemVer 2 version of chart description str A one-sentence description of chart [optional] keywords list[str] A list of string keywords [optional] engine str The name of template engine icon str The URL to an icon file api_version str The API version of this chart app_version str The version of the application enclosed in the chart deprecated bool Whether or not this chart is deprecated [optional]</description></item><item><title>ChartVersion</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/chartversion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/chartversion/</guid><description>ChartVersion Properties Name Type Description Notes labels list[Label] A list of label [optional] created str The created time of the chart entry [optional] removed bool A flag to indicate if the chart entry is removed [optional] digest str The digest value of the chart entry [optional] urls list[str] The urls of the chart entry [optional]</description></item><item><title>ComponentHealthStatus</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/componenthealthstatus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/componenthealthstatus/</guid><description>ComponentHealthStatus Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The component name [optional] status str The health status of component [optional] error str (optional) The error message when the status is &amp;amp;quot;unhealthy&amp;amp;quot; [optional]</description></item><item><title>Configurations</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurations/</guid><description>Configurations Properties Name Type Description Notes auth_mode str The auth mode of current system, such as &amp;amp;quot;db_auth&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;ldap_auth&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;oidc_auth&amp;amp;quot; [optional] ldap_base_dn str The Base DN for LDAP binding. [optional] ldap_filter str The filter for LDAP search [optional] ldap_group_base_dn str The base DN to search LDAP group. [optional] ldap_group_admin_dn str Specify the ldap group which have the same privilege with Harbor admin [optional] ldap_group_attribute_name str The attribute which is used as identity of the LDAP group, default is cn.</description></item><item><title>ConfigurationsResponse</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurationsresponse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurationsresponse/</guid><description>ConfigurationsResponse Properties Name Type Description Notes auth_mode StringConfigItem The auth mode of current system, such as &amp;amp;quot;db_auth&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;ldap_auth&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;oidc_auth&amp;amp;quot; [optional] ldap_base_dn StringConfigItem The Base DN for LDAP binding. [optional] ldap_filter StringConfigItem The filter for LDAP search [optional] ldap_group_base_dn StringConfigItem The base DN to search LDAP group. [optional] ldap_group_admin_dn StringConfigItem Specify the ldap group which have the same privilege with Harbor admin [optional] ldap_group_attribute_name StringConfigItem The attribute which is used as identity of the LDAP group, default is cn.</description></item><item><title>ConfigurationsResponseScanAllPolicy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurationsresponsescanallpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurationsresponsescanallpolicy/</guid><description>ConfigurationsResponseScanAllPolicy Properties Name Type Description Notes type str The type of scan all policy, currently the valid values are &amp;amp;quot;none&amp;amp;quot; and &amp;amp;quot;daily&amp;amp;quot; [optional] parameter ConfigurationsResponseScanAllPolicyParameter [optional]</description></item><item><title>ConfigurationsResponseScanAllPolicyParameter</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurationsresponsescanallpolicyparameter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/configurationsresponsescanallpolicyparameter/</guid><description>ConfigurationsResponseScanAllPolicyParameter Properties Name Type Description Notes daily_time int The offset in seconds of UTC 0 o'clock, only valid when the policy type is &amp;amp;quot;daily&amp;amp;quot; [optional]</description></item><item><title>CVEAllowlist</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/cveallowlist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/cveallowlist/</guid><description>CVEAllowlist Properties Name Type Description Notes id int ID of the allowlist [optional] project_id int ID of the project which the allowlist belongs to. For system level allowlist this attribute is zero. [optional] expires_at int the time for expiration of the allowlist, in the form of seconds since epoch. This is an optional attribute, if it's not set the CVE allowlist does not expire. [optional] items list[CVEAllowlistItem] [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the allowlist.</description></item><item><title>CVEAllowlistItem</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/cveallowlistitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/cveallowlistitem/</guid><description>CVEAllowlistItem Properties Name Type Description Notes cve_id str The ID of the CVE, such as &amp;amp;quot;CVE-2019-10164&amp;amp;quot; [optional]</description></item><item><title>Endpoint</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/endpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/endpoint/</guid><description>Endpoint Properties Name Type Description Notes url str The URL of OIDC endpoint to be tested. [optional] verify_cert bool Whether the certificate should be verified [optional]</description></item><item><title>Error</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/error/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/error/</guid><description>Error Properties Name Type Description Notes code str The error code [optional] message str The error message [optional]</description></item><item><title>Errors</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/errors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/errors/</guid><description>Errors Properties Name Type Description Notes errors list[Error] [optional]</description></item><item><title>EventType</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/eventtype/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/eventtype/</guid><description>EventType Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>ExecHistory</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/exechistory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/exechistory/</guid><description>ExecHistory Properties Name Type Description Notes id int the id of purge job. [optional] job_name str the job name of purge job. [optional] job_kind str the job kind of purge job. [optional] job_parameters str the job parameters of purge job. [optional] schedule ScheduleObj [optional] job_status str the status of purge job. [optional] deleted bool if purge job was deleted. [optional] creation_time datetime the creation time of purge job. [optional] update_time datetime the update time of purge job.</description></item><item><title>Execution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/execution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/execution/</guid><description>Execution Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of execution [optional] vendor_type str The vendor type of execution [optional] vendor_id int The vendor id of execution [optional] status str The status of execution [optional] status_message str The status message of execution [optional] metrics Metrics [optional] trigger str The trigger of execution [optional] extra_attrs ExtraAttrs [optional] start_time str The start time of execution [optional] end_time str The end time of execution [optional]</description></item><item><title>ExtraAttrs</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/extraattrs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/extraattrs/</guid><description>ExtraAttrs Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>FilterStyle</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/filterstyle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/filterstyle/</guid><description>FilterStyle Properties Name Type Description Notes type str The filter type [optional] style str The filter style [optional] values list[str] The filter values [optional]</description></item><item><title>GCHistory</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/gchistory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/gchistory/</guid><description>GCHistory Properties Name Type Description Notes id int the id of gc job. [optional] job_name str the job name of gc job. [optional] job_kind str the job kind of gc job. [optional] job_parameters str the job parameters of gc job. [optional] schedule ScheduleObj [optional] job_status str the status of gc job. [optional] deleted bool if gc job was deleted. [optional] creation_time datetime the creation time of gc job. [optional] update_time datetime the update time of gc job.</description></item><item><title>GeneralInfo</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/generalinfo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/generalinfo/</guid><description>GeneralInfo Properties Name Type Description Notes current_time datetime The current time of the server. [optional] with_notary bool If the Harbor instance is deployed with nested notary. [optional] with_chartmuseum bool If the Harbor instance is deployed with nested chartmuseum. [optional] registry_url str The url of registry against which the docker command should be issued. [optional] external_url str The external URL of Harbor, with protocol. [optional] auth_mode str The auth mode of current Harbor instance.</description></item><item><title>Icon</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/icon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/icon/</guid><description>Icon Properties Name Type Description Notes content_type str The content type of the icon [optional] content str The base64 encoded content of the icon [optional]</description></item><item><title>ImmutableRule</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/immutablerule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/immutablerule/</guid><description>ImmutableRule Properties Name Type Description Notes id int [optional] priority int [optional] disabled bool [optional] action str [optional] template str [optional] params dict(str, object) [optional] tag_selectors list[ImmutableSelector] [optional] scope_selectors dict(str, list[ImmutableSelector]) [optional]</description></item><item><title>ImmutableSelector</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/immutableselector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/immutableselector/</guid><description>ImmutableSelector Properties Name Type Description Notes kind str [optional] decoration str [optional] pattern str [optional] extras str [optional]</description></item><item><title>Instance</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/instance/</guid><description>Instance Properties Name Type Description Notes id int Unique ID [optional] name str Instance name [optional] description str Description of instance [optional] vendor str Based on which driver, identified by ID [optional] endpoint str The service endpoint of this instance [optional] auth_mode str The authentication way supported [optional] auth_info dict(str, str) The auth credential data if exists [optional] status str The health status [optional] enabled bool Whether the instance is activated or not [optional] default bool Whether the instance is default or not [optional] insecure bool Whether the instance endpoint is insecure or not [optional] setup_timestamp int The timestamp of instance setting up [optional]</description></item><item><title>IntegerConfigItem</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/integerconfigitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/integerconfigitem/</guid><description>IntegerConfigItem Properties Name Type Description Notes value int The integer value of current config item [optional] editable bool The configure item can be updated or not [optional]</description></item><item><title>InternalConfigurationsResponse</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/internalconfigurationsresponse/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/internalconfigurationsresponse/</guid><description>InternalConfigurationsResponse Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>InternalConfigurationValue</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/internalconfigurationvalue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/internalconfigurationvalue/</guid><description>InternalConfigurationValue Properties Name Type Description Notes value object The value of current config item [optional] editable bool The configure item can be updated or not [optional]</description></item><item><title>IsDefault</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/isdefault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/isdefault/</guid><description>IsDefault Properties Name Type Description Notes is_default bool A flag indicating whether a scanner registration is default. [optional]</description></item><item><title>JobQueue</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/jobqueue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/jobqueue/</guid><description>JobQueue Properties Name Type Description Notes job_type str The type of the job queue [optional] count int The count of jobs in the job queue [optional] latency int The latency the job queue (seconds) [optional] paused bool The paused status of the job queue [optional]</description></item><item><title>Label</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/label/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/label/</guid><description>Label Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the label [optional] name str The name the label [optional] description str The description the label [optional] color str The color the label [optional] scope str The scope the label [optional] project_id int The ID of project that the label belongs to [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time the label [optional] update_time datetime The update time of the label [optional]</description></item><item><title>LdapConf</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapconf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapconf/</guid><description>LdapConf Properties Name Type Description Notes ldap_url str The url of ldap service. [optional] ldap_search_dn str The search dn of ldap service. [optional] ldap_search_password str The search password of ldap service. [optional] ldap_base_dn str The base dn of ldap service. [optional] ldap_filter str The serach filter of ldap service. [optional] ldap_uid str The serach uid from ldap service attributes. [optional] ldap_scope int The serach scope of ldap service. [optional] ldap_connection_timeout int The connect timeout of ldap service(second).</description></item><item><title>LdapFailedImportUser</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapfailedimportuser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapfailedimportuser/</guid><description>LdapFailedImportUser Properties Name Type Description Notes uid str the uid can't add to system. [optional] error str fail reason. [optional]</description></item><item><title>LdapImportUsers</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapimportusers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapimportusers/</guid><description>LdapImportUsers Properties Name Type Description Notes ldap_uid_list list[str] selected uid list [optional]</description></item><item><title>LdapPingResult</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldappingresult/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldappingresult/</guid><description>LdapPingResult Properties Name Type Description Notes success bool Test success [optional] message str The ping operation output message. [optional]</description></item><item><title>LdapUser</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapuser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/ldapuser/</guid><description>LdapUser Properties Name Type Description Notes username str ldap username. [optional] realname str The user realname from &amp;amp;quot;uid&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;cn&amp;amp;quot; attribute. [optional] email str The user email address from &amp;amp;quot;mail&amp;amp;quot; or &amp;amp;quot;email&amp;amp;quot; attribute. [optional]</description></item><item><title>Metadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/metadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/metadata/</guid><description>Metadata Properties Name Type Description Notes id str id [optional] name str name [optional] icon str icon [optional] maintainers list[str] maintainers [optional] version str version [optional] source str source [optional]</description></item><item><title>Metrics</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/metrics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/metrics/</guid><description>Metrics Properties Name Type Description Notes task_count int The count of task [optional] success_task_count int The count of success task [optional] error_task_count int The count of error task [optional] pending_task_count int The count of pending task [optional] running_task_count int The count of running task [optional] scheduled_task_count int The count of scheduled task [optional] stopped_task_count int The count of stopped task [optional]</description></item><item><title>NativeReportSummary</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/nativereportsummary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/nativereportsummary/</guid><description>NativeReportSummary Properties Name Type Description Notes report_id str id of the native scan report [optional] scan_status str The status of the report generating process [optional] severity str The overall severity [optional] duration int The seconds spent for generating the report [optional] summary VulnerabilitySummary [optional] start_time datetime The start time of the scan process that generating report [optional] end_time datetime The end time of the scan process that generating report [optional] complete_percent int The complete percent of the scanning which value is between 0 and 100 [optional] scanner Scanner [optional]</description></item><item><title>NotifyType</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/notifytype/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/notifytype/</guid><description>NotifyType Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>OIDC configuration for Azure AD</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-guide/oidc-configuration-for-azure-ad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-guide/oidc-configuration-for-azure-ad/</guid><description>How to Set up Azure Active Directory as OIDC Provider for Your Harbor Container Registry This guide will walk you through the setup of Harbor with Azure AD (Azure Active Directory) using OIDC (OpenID Connect).
The other tutorial explains what you should do in your Container Registry instance if you want to use OIDC authentication in general. However, before doing anything in Container Registry, you need to complete the configuration on the provider side.</description></item><item><title>OIDCCliSecretReq</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/oidcclisecretreq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/oidcclisecretreq/</guid><description>OIDCCliSecretReq Properties Name Type Description Notes secret str The new secret [optional]</description></item><item><title>OIDCUserInfo</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/oidcuserinfo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/oidcuserinfo/</guid><description>OIDCUserInfo Properties Name Type Description Notes id int the ID of the OIDC info record [optional] user_id int the ID of the user [optional] subiss str the concatenation of sub and issuer in the ID token [optional] secret str the secret of the OIDC user that can be used for CLI to push/pull artifacts [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the OIDC user info record. [optional] update_time datetime The update time of the OIDC user info record.</description></item><item><title>OverallHealthStatus</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/overallhealthstatus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/overallhealthstatus/</guid><description>OverallHealthStatus Properties Name Type Description Notes status str The overall health status. It is &amp;amp;quot;healthy&amp;amp;quot; only when all the components' status are &amp;amp;quot;healthy&amp;amp;quot; [optional] components list[ComponentHealthStatus] [optional]</description></item><item><title>PasswordReq</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/passwordreq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/passwordreq/</guid><description>PasswordReq Properties Name Type Description Notes old_password str The user's existing password. [optional] new_password str New password for marking as to be updated. [optional]</description></item><item><title>Permission</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/permission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/permission/</guid><description>Permission Properties Name Type Description Notes resource str The permission resoruce [optional] action str The permission action [optional]</description></item><item><title>Platform</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/platform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/platform/</guid><description>Platform Properties Name Type Description Notes architecture str The architecture that the artifact applys to [optional] os str The OS that the artifact applys to [optional] os_version str The version of the OS that the artifact applys to [optional] os_features list[str] The features of the OS that the artifact applys to [optional] variant str The variant of the CPU [optional]</description></item><item><title>PreheatPolicy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/preheatpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/preheatpolicy/</guid><description>PreheatPolicy Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of preheat policy [optional] name str The Name of preheat policy [optional] description str The Description of preheat policy [optional] project_id int The ID of preheat policy project [optional] provider_id int The ID of preheat policy provider [optional] provider_name str The Name of preheat policy provider [optional] filters str The Filters of preheat policy [optional] trigger str The Trigger of preheat policy [optional] enabled bool Whether the preheat policy enabled [optional] creation_time datetime The Create Time of preheat policy [optional] update_time datetime The Update Time of preheat policy [optional]</description></item><item><title>Project</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/project/</guid><description>Project Properties Name Type Description Notes project_id int Project ID [optional] owner_id int The owner ID of the project always means the creator of the project. [optional] name str The name of the project. [optional] registry_id int The ID of referenced registry when the project is a proxy cache project. [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the project. [optional] update_time datetime The update time of the project. [optional] deleted bool A deletion mark of the project.</description></item><item><title>ProjectDeletable</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectdeletable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectdeletable/</guid><description>ProjectDeletable Properties Name Type Description Notes deletable bool Whether the project can be deleted. [optional] message str The detail message when the project can not be deleted. [optional]</description></item><item><title>ProjectMember</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectmember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectmember/</guid><description>ProjectMember Properties Name Type Description Notes role_id int The role id 1 for projectAdmin, 2 for developer, 3 for guest, 4 for maintainer [optional] member_user UserEntity [optional] member_group UserGroup [optional]</description></item><item><title>ProjectMemberEntity</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectmemberentity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectmemberentity/</guid><description>ProjectMemberEntity Properties Name Type Description Notes id int the project member id [optional] project_id int the project id [optional] entity_name str the name of the group member. [optional] role_name str the name of the role [optional] role_id int the role id [optional] entity_id int the id of entity, if the member is a user, it is user_id in user table. if the member is a user group, it is the user group's ID in user_group table.</description></item><item><title>ProjectMetadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectmetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectmetadata/</guid><description>ProjectMetadata Properties Name Type Description Notes public str The public status of the project. The valid values are &amp;amp;quot;true&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;false&amp;amp;quot;. [optional] enable_content_trust str Whether content trust is enabled or not. If it is enabled, user can't pull unsigned images from this project. The valid values are &amp;amp;quot;true&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;false&amp;amp;quot;. [optional] enable_content_trust_cosign str Whether cosign content trust is enabled or not. If it is enabled, user can't pull images without cosign signature from this project.</description></item><item><title>ProjectReq</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectreq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectreq/</guid><description>ProjectReq Properties Name Type Description Notes project_name str The name of the project. [optional] public bool deprecated, reserved for project creation in replication [optional] metadata ProjectMetadata The metadata of the project. [optional] cve_allowlist CVEAllowlist The CVE allowlist of the project. [optional] storage_limit int The storage quota of the project. [optional] registry_id int The ID of referenced registry when creating the proxy cache project [optional]</description></item><item><title>ProjectScanner</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectscanner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectscanner/</guid><description>ProjectScanner Properties Name Type Description Notes uuid str The identifier of the scanner registration</description></item><item><title>ProjectSummary</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectsummary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectsummary/</guid><description>ProjectSummary Properties Name Type Description Notes repo_count int The number of the repositories under this project. [optional] chart_count int The total number of charts under this project. [optional] project_admin_count int The total number of project admin members. [optional] maintainer_count int The total number of maintainer members. [optional] developer_count int The total number of developer members. [optional] guest_count int The total number of guest members. [optional] limited_guest_count int The total number of limited guest members.</description></item><item><title>ProjectSummaryQuota</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectsummaryquota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/projectsummaryquota/</guid><description>ProjectSummaryQuota Properties Name Type Description Notes hard ResourceList The hard limits of the quota [optional] used ResourceList The used status of the quota [optional]</description></item><item><title>ProviderUnderProject</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/providerunderproject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/providerunderproject/</guid><description>ProviderUnderProject Properties Name Type Description Notes id int [optional] provider str [optional] enabled bool [optional] default bool [optional]</description></item><item><title>Quota</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/quota/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/quota/</guid><description>Quota Properties Name Type Description Notes id int ID of the quota [optional] ref QuotaRefObject The reference object of the quota [optional] hard ResourceList The hard limits of the quota [optional] used ResourceList The used status of the quota [optional] creation_time datetime the creation time of the quota [optional] update_time datetime the update time of the quota [optional]</description></item><item><title>QuotaRefObject</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/quotarefobject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/quotarefobject/</guid><description>QuotaRefObject Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>QuotaUpdateReq</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/quotaupdatereq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/quotaupdatereq/</guid><description>QuotaUpdateReq Properties Name Type Description Notes hard ResourceList The new hard limits for the quota [optional]</description></item><item><title>Reference</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/reference/</guid><description>Reference Properties Name Type Description Notes parent_id int The parent ID of the reference [optional] child_id int The child ID of the reference [optional] child_digest str The digest of the child artifact [optional] platform Platform [optional] annotations Annotations [optional] urls list[str] The download URLs [optional]</description></item><item><title>Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registry/</guid><description>Registry Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The registry ID. [optional] url str The registry URL string. [optional] name str The registry name. [optional] credential RegistryCredential [optional] type str Type of the registry, e.g. 'harbor'. [optional] insecure bool Whether or not the certificate will be verified when Harbor tries to access the server. [optional] description str Description of the registry. [optional] status str Health status of the registry. [optional] creation_time datetime The create time of the policy.</description></item><item><title>RegistryCredential</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registrycredential/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registrycredential/</guid><description>RegistryCredential Properties Name Type Description Notes type str Credential type, such as 'basic', 'oauth'. [optional] access_key str Access key, e.g. user name when credential type is 'basic'. [optional] access_secret str Access secret, e.g. password when credential type is 'basic'. [optional]</description></item><item><title>RegistryEndpoint</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryendpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryendpoint/</guid><description>RegistryEndpoint Properties Name Type Description Notes key str The endpoint key [optional] value str The endpoint value [optional]</description></item><item><title>RegistryInfo</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryinfo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryinfo/</guid><description>RegistryInfo Properties Name Type Description Notes type str The registry type [optional] description str The description [optional] supported_resource_filters list[FilterStyle] The filters that the registry supports [optional] supported_triggers list[str] The triggers that the registry supports [optional] supported_copy_by_chunk bool The registry whether support copy by chunk. [optional]</description></item><item><title>RegistryPing</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryping/</guid><description>RegistryPing Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The registry ID. [optional] type str Type of the registry, e.g. 'harbor'. [optional] url str The registry URL. [optional] credential_type str Credential type of the registry, e.g. 'basic'. [optional] access_key str The registry access key. [optional] access_secret str The registry access secret. [optional] insecure bool Whether or not the certificate will be verified when Harbor tries to access the server. [optional]</description></item><item><title>RegistryProviderCredentialPattern</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryprovidercredentialpattern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryprovidercredentialpattern/</guid><description>RegistryProviderCredentialPattern Properties Name Type Description Notes access_key_type str The access key type [optional] access_key_data str The access key data [optional] access_secret_type str The access secret type [optional] access_secret_data str The access secret data [optional]</description></item><item><title>RegistryProviderEndpointPattern</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryproviderendpointpattern/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryproviderendpointpattern/</guid><description>RegistryProviderEndpointPattern Properties Name Type Description Notes endpoint_type str The endpoint type [optional] endpoints list[RegistryEndpoint] The endpoint list [optional]</description></item><item><title>RegistryProviderInfo</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryproviderinfo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryproviderinfo/</guid><description>RegistryProviderInfo Properties Name Type Description Notes endpoint_pattern RegistryProviderEndpointPattern The endpoint pattern [optional] credential_pattern RegistryProviderCredentialPattern The credential pattern [optional]</description></item><item><title>RegistryUpdate</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryupdate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/registryupdate/</guid><description>RegistryUpdate Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The registry name. [optional] description str Description of the registry. [optional] url str The registry URL. [optional] credential_type str Credential type of the registry, e.g. 'basic'. [optional] access_key str The registry access key. [optional] access_secret str The registry access secret. [optional] insecure bool Whether or not the certificate will be verified when Harbor tries to access the server. [optional]</description></item><item><title>ReplicationExecution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationexecution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationexecution/</guid><description>ReplicationExecution Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the execution [optional] policy_id int The ID if the policy that the execution belongs to [optional] status str The status of the execution [optional] trigger str The trigger mode [optional] start_time datetime The start time [optional] end_time datetime The end time [optional] status_text str The status text [optional] total int The total count of all executions [optional] failed int The count of failed executions [optional] succeed int The count of succeed executions [optional] in_progress int The count of in_progress executions [optional] stopped int The count of stopped executions [optional]</description></item><item><title>ReplicationFilter</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationfilter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationfilter/</guid><description>ReplicationFilter Properties Name Type Description Notes type str The replication policy filter type. [optional] value object The value of replication policy filter. [optional] decoration str matches or excludes the result [optional]</description></item><item><title>ReplicationPolicy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationpolicy/</guid><description>ReplicationPolicy Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The policy ID. [optional] name str The policy name. [optional] description str The description of the policy. [optional] src_registry Registry The source registry. [optional] dest_registry Registry The destination registry. [optional] dest_namespace str The destination namespace. [optional] dest_namespace_replace_count int Specify how many path components will be replaced by the provided destination namespace. The default value is -1 in which case the legacy mode will be applied.</description></item><item><title>ReplicationTask</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationtask/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationtask/</guid><description>ReplicationTask Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the task [optional] execution_id int The ID of the execution that the task belongs to [optional] status str The status of the task [optional] job_id str The ID of the underlying job that the task related to [optional] operation str The operation of the task [optional] resource_type str The type of the resource that the task operates [optional] src_resource str The source resource that the task operates [optional] dst_resource str The destination resource that the task operates [optional] start_time datetime The start time of the task [optional] end_time datetime The end time of the task [optional]</description></item><item><title>ReplicationTrigger</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationtrigger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationtrigger/</guid><description>ReplicationTrigger Properties Name Type Description Notes type str The replication policy trigger type. The valid values are manual, event_based and scheduled. [optional] trigger_settings ReplicationTriggerSettings [optional]</description></item><item><title>ReplicationTriggerSettings</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationtriggersettings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/replicationtriggersettings/</guid><description>ReplicationTriggerSettings Properties Name Type Description Notes cron str The cron string for scheduled trigger [optional]</description></item><item><title>Repository</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/repository/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/repository/</guid><description>Repository Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the repository [optional] project_id int The ID of the project that the repository belongs to [optional] name str The name of the repository [optional] description str The description of the repository [optional] artifact_count int The count of the artifacts inside the repository [optional] pull_count int The count that the artifact inside the repository pulled [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the repository [optional] update_time datetime The update time of the repository [optional]</description></item><item><title>ResourceList</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/resourcelist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/resourcelist/</guid><description>ResourceList Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>RetentionExecution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionexecution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionexecution/</guid><description>RetentionExecution Properties Name Type Description Notes id int [optional] policy_id int [optional] start_time str [optional] end_time str [optional] status str [optional] trigger str [optional] dry_run bool [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionExecutionTask</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionexecutiontask/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionexecutiontask/</guid><description>RetentionExecutionTask Properties Name Type Description Notes id int [optional] execution_id int [optional] repository str [optional] job_id str [optional] status str [optional] status_code int [optional] status_revision int [optional] start_time str [optional] end_time str [optional] total int [optional] retained int [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionMetadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionmetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionmetadata/</guid><description>RetentionMetadata Properties Name Type Description Notes templates list[RetentionRuleMetadata] templates [optional] scope_selectors list[RetentionSelectorMetadata] supported scope selectors [optional] tag_selectors list[RetentionSelectorMetadata] supported tag selectors [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionPolicy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionpolicy/</guid><description>RetentionPolicy Properties Name Type Description Notes id int [optional] algorithm str [optional] rules list[RetentionRule] [optional] trigger RetentionRuleTrigger [optional] scope RetentionPolicyScope [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionPolicyScope</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionpolicyscope/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionpolicyscope/</guid><description>RetentionPolicyScope Properties Name Type Description Notes level str [optional] ref int [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionRule</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionrule/</guid><description>RetentionRule Properties Name Type Description Notes id int [optional] priority int [optional] disabled bool [optional] action str [optional] template str [optional] params dict(str, object) [optional] tag_selectors list[RetentionSelector] [optional] scope_selectors dict(str, list[RetentionSelector]) [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionRuleMetadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionrulemetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionrulemetadata/</guid><description>RetentionRuleMetadata Properties Name Type Description Notes rule_template str rule id [optional] display_text str rule display text [optional] action str rule action [optional] params list[RetentionRuleParamMetadata] rule params [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionRuleParamMetadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionruleparammetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionruleparammetadata/</guid><description>RetentionRuleParamMetadata Properties Name Type Description Notes type str [optional] unit str [optional] required bool [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionRuleTrigger</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionruletrigger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionruletrigger/</guid><description>RetentionRuleTrigger Properties Name Type Description Notes kind str [optional] settings object [optional] references object [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionSelector</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionselector/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionselector/</guid><description>RetentionSelector Properties Name Type Description Notes kind str [optional] decoration str [optional] pattern str [optional] extras str [optional]</description></item><item><title>RetentionSelectorMetadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionselectormetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/retentionselectormetadata/</guid><description>RetentionSelectorMetadata Properties Name Type Description Notes display_text str [optional] kind str [optional] decorations list[str] [optional]</description></item><item><title>Robot</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robot/</guid><description>Robot Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the robot [optional] name str The name of the tag [optional] description str The description of the robot [optional] secret str The secret of the robot [optional] level str The level of the robot, project or system [optional] duration int The duration of the robot in days [optional] editable bool The editable status of the robot [optional] disable bool The disable status of the robot [optional] expires_at int The expiration data of the robot [optional] permissions list[RobotPermission] [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the robot.</description></item><item><title>RobotCreate</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotcreate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotcreate/</guid><description>RobotCreate Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The name of the tag [optional] description str The description of the robot [optional] secret str The secret of the robot [optional] level str The level of the robot, project or system [optional] disable bool The disable status of the robot [optional] duration int The duration of the robot in days [optional] permissions list[RobotPermission] [optional]</description></item><item><title>RobotCreated</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotcreated/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotcreated/</guid><description>RobotCreated Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the robot [optional] name str The name of the tag [optional] secret str The secret of the robot [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the robot. [optional] expires_at int The expiration data of the robot [optional]</description></item><item><title>RobotCreateV1</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotcreatev1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotcreatev1/</guid><description>RobotCreateV1 Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The name of robot account [optional] description str The description of robot account [optional] expires_at int The expiration time on or after which the JWT MUST NOT be accepted for processing. [optional] access list[Access] The permission of robot account [optional]</description></item><item><title>RobotPermission</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotpermission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotpermission/</guid><description>RobotPermission Properties Name Type Description Notes kind str The kind of the permission [optional] namespace str The namespace of the permission [optional] access list[Access] [optional]</description></item><item><title>RobotSec</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotsec/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/robotsec/</guid><description>RobotSec Properties Name Type Description Notes secret str The secret of the robot [optional]</description></item><item><title>RoleRequest</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/rolerequest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/rolerequest/</guid><description>RoleRequest Properties Name Type Description Notes role_id int The role id 1 for projectAdmin, 2 for developer, 3 for guest, 4 for maintainer [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScanDataExportExecution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportexecution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportexecution/</guid><description>ScanDataExportExecution Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the execution [optional] user_id int The ID if the user triggering the export job [optional] status str The status of the execution [optional] trigger str The trigger mode [optional] start_time datetime The start time [optional] end_time datetime The end time [optional] status_text str The status text [optional] user_name str The name of the user triggering the job [optional] file_present bool Indicates whether the export artifact is present in registry [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScanDataExportExecutionList</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportexecutionlist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportexecutionlist/</guid><description>ScanDataExportExecutionList Properties Name Type Description Notes items list[ScanDataExportExecution] The list of scan data export executions [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScanDataExportJob</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportjob/</guid><description>ScanDataExportJob Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The id of the scan data export job [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScanDataExportRequest</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportrequest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scandataexportrequest/</guid><description>ScanDataExportRequest Properties Name Type Description Notes job_name str Name of the scan data export job [optional] projects list[int] A list of one or more projects for which to export the scan data, currently only one project is supported due to performance concerns, but define as array for extension in the future. [optional] labels list[int] A list of one or more labels for which to export the scan data, defaults to all if empty [optional] repositories str A list of repositories for which to export the scan data, defaults to all if empty [optional] cve_ids str CVE-IDs for which to export data.</description></item><item><title>Scanner</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scanner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scanner/</guid><description>Scanner Properties Name Type Description Notes name str Name of the scanner [optional] vendor str Name of the scanner provider [optional] version str Version of the scanner adapter [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScannerAdapterMetadata</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scanneradaptermetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scanneradaptermetadata/</guid><description>ScannerAdapterMetadata Properties Name Type Description Notes scanner Scanner [optional] capabilities list[ScannerCapability] [optional] properties dict(str, str) [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScannerCapability</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannercapability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannercapability/</guid><description>ScannerCapability Properties Name Type Description Notes consumes_mime_types list[str] [optional] produces_mime_types list[str] [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScannerRegistration</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannerregistration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannerregistration/</guid><description>ScannerRegistration Properties Name Type Description Notes uuid str The unique identifier of this registration. [optional] name str The name of this registration. [optional] description str An optional description of this registration. [optional] url str A base URL of the scanner adapter [optional] disabled bool Indicate whether the registration is enabled or not [optional] [default to False] is_default bool Indicate if the registration is set as the system default one [optional] [default to False] auth str Specify what authentication approach is adopted for the HTTP communications.</description></item><item><title>ScannerRegistrationReq</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannerregistrationreq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannerregistrationreq/</guid><description>ScannerRegistrationReq Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The name of this registration description str An optional description of this registration. [optional] url str A base URL of the scanner adapter. auth str Specify what authentication approach is adopted for the HTTP communications. Supported types Basic&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;Bearer&amp;amp;quot; and api key header &amp;amp;quot;X-ScannerAdapter-API-Key&amp;amp;quot; [optional] access_credential str An optional value of the HTTP Authorization header sent with each request to the Scanner Adapter API.</description></item><item><title>ScannerRegistrationSettings</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannerregistrationsettings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scannerregistrationsettings/</guid><description>ScannerRegistrationSettings Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The name of this registration url str A base URL of the scanner adapter. auth str Specify what authentication approach is adopted for the HTTP communications. Supported types Basic&amp;amp;quot;, &amp;amp;quot;Bearer&amp;amp;quot; and api key header &amp;amp;quot;X-ScannerAdapter-API-Key&amp;amp;quot; [optional] [default to &amp;lsquo;&amp;rsquo;] access_credential str An optional value of the HTTP Authorization header sent with each request to the Scanner Adapter API. [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScanOverview</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scanoverview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scanoverview/</guid><description>ScanOverview Properties Name Type Description Notes</description></item><item><title>Schedule</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/schedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/schedule/</guid><description>Schedule Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The id of the schedule. [optional] status str The status of the schedule. [optional] creation_time datetime the creation time of the schedule. [optional] update_time datetime the update time of the schedule. [optional] schedule ScheduleObj [optional] parameters dict(str, object) The parameters of schedule job [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScheduleObj</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scheduleobj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scheduleobj/</guid><description>ScheduleObj Properties Name Type Description Notes type str The schedule type. The valid values are 'Hourly', 'Daily', 'Weekly', 'Custom', 'Manual' and 'None'. 'Manual' means to trigger it right away and 'None' means to cancel the schedule. [optional] cron str A cron expression, a time-based job scheduler. [optional] next_scheduled_time datetime The next time to schedule to run the job. [optional]</description></item><item><title>SchedulerStatus</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/schedulerstatus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/schedulerstatus/</guid><description>SchedulerStatus Properties Name Type Description Notes paused bool if the scheduler is paused [optional]</description></item><item><title>ScheduleTask</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scheduletask/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/scheduletask/</guid><description>ScheduleTask Properties Name Type Description Notes id int the id of the Schedule task [optional] vendor_type str the vendor type of the current schedule task [optional] vendor_id int the vendor id of the current task [optional] cron str the cron of the current schedule task [optional] update_time datetime the update time of the schedule task [optional]</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/search/</guid><description>Search Properties Name Type Description Notes project list[Project] Search results of the projects that matched the filter keywords. [optional] repository list[SearchRepository] Search results of the repositories that matched the filter keywords. [optional] chart list[SearchResult] Search results of the charts that macthed the filter keywords. [optional]</description></item><item><title>SearchRepository</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/searchrepository/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/searchrepository/</guid><description>SearchRepository Properties Name Type Description Notes project_id int The ID of the project that the repository belongs to [optional] project_name str The name of the project that the repository belongs to [optional] project_public bool The flag to indicate the publicity of the project that the repository belongs to (1 is public, 0 is not) [optional] repository_name str The name of the repository [optional] pull_count int The count how many times the repository is pulled [optional] artifact_count int The count of artifacts in the repository [optional]</description></item><item><title>SearchResult</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/searchresult/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/searchresult/</guid><description>SearchResult Properties Name Type Description Notes name str The chart name with repo name [optional] score int The matched level [optional] chart ChartVersion [optional]</description></item><item><title>StartReplicationExecution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/startreplicationexecution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/startreplicationexecution/</guid><description>StartReplicationExecution Properties Name Type Description Notes policy_id int The ID of policy that the execution belongs to. [optional]</description></item><item><title>Statistic</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/statistic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/statistic/</guid><description>Statistic Properties Name Type Description Notes private_project_count int The count of the private projects [optional] private_repo_count int The count of the private repositories [optional] public_project_count int The count of the public projects [optional] public_repo_count int The count of the public repositories [optional] total_project_count int The count of the total projects, only be seen by the system admin [optional] total_repo_count int The count of the total repositories, only be seen by the system admin [optional] total_storage_consumption int The total storage consumption of blobs, only be seen by the system admin [optional]</description></item><item><title>Stats</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/stats/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/stats/</guid><description>Stats Properties Name Type Description Notes total int The total number of scan processes triggered by the scan all action [optional] completed int The number of the finished scan processes triggered by the scan all action [optional] metrics dict(str, int) The metrics data for the each status [optional] ongoing bool A flag indicating job status of scan all. [optional] trigger str The trigger of the scan all job. [optional]</description></item><item><title>Storage</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/storage/</guid><description>Storage Properties Name Type Description Notes total int Total volume size. [optional] free int Free volume size. [optional]</description></item><item><title>StringConfigItem</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/stringconfigitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/stringconfigitem/</guid><description>StringConfigItem Properties Name Type Description Notes value str The string value of current config item [optional] editable bool The configure item can be updated or not [optional]</description></item><item><title>SupportedWebhookEventTypes</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/supportedwebhookeventtypes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/supportedwebhookeventtypes/</guid><description>SupportedWebhookEventTypes Properties Name Type Description Notes event_type list[EventType] [optional] notify_type list[NotifyType] [optional]</description></item><item><title>SystemInfo</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/systeminfo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/systeminfo/</guid><description>SystemInfo Properties Name Type Description Notes storage list[Storage] The storage of system. [optional]</description></item><item><title>Tag</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/tag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/tag/</guid><description>Tag Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the tag [optional] repository_id int The ID of the repository that the tag belongs to [optional] artifact_id int The ID of the artifact that the tag attached to [optional] name str The name of the tag [optional] push_time datetime The push time of the tag [optional] pull_time datetime The latest pull time of the tag [optional] immutable bool The immutable status of the tag [optional] signed bool The attribute indicates whether the tag is signed or not [optional]</description></item><item><title>Task</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/task/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/task/</guid><description>Task Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of task [optional] execution_id int The ID of task execution [optional] status str The status of task [optional] status_message str The status message of task [optional] run_count int The count of task run [optional] extra_attrs ExtraAttrs [optional] creation_time str The creation time of task [optional] update_time str The update time of task [optional] start_time str The start time of task [optional] end_time str The end time of task [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserCreationReq</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usercreationreq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usercreationreq/</guid><description>UserCreationReq Properties Name Type Description Notes email str [optional] realname str [optional] comment str [optional] password str [optional] username str [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserEntity</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/userentity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/userentity/</guid><description>UserEntity Properties Name Type Description Notes user_id int The ID of the user. [optional] username str The name of the user. [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserGroup</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usergroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usergroup/</guid><description>UserGroup Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the user group [optional] group_name str The name of the user group [optional] group_type int The group type, 1 for LDAP group, 2 for HTTP group, 3 for OIDC group. [optional] ldap_group_dn str The DN of the LDAP group if group type is 1 (LDAP group). [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserGroupSearchItem</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usergroupsearchitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usergroupsearchitem/</guid><description>UserGroupSearchItem Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The ID of the user group [optional] group_name str The name of the user group [optional] group_type int The group type, 1 for LDAP group, 2 for HTTP group, 3 for OIDC group. [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserProfile</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/userprofile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/userprofile/</guid><description>UserProfile Properties Name Type Description Notes email str [optional] realname str [optional] comment str [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserResp</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/userresp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/userresp/</guid><description>UserResp Properties Name Type Description Notes email str [optional] realname str [optional] comment str [optional] user_id int [optional] username str [optional] sysadmin_flag bool [optional] admin_role_in_auth bool indicate the admin privilege is grant by authenticator (LDAP), is always false unless it is the current login user [optional] oidc_user_meta OIDCUserInfo [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of the user. [optional] update_time datetime The update time of the user. [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserSearch</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usersearch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usersearch/</guid><description>UserSearch Properties Name Type Description Notes user_id int The ID of the user. [optional] username str [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserSearchRespItem</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usersearchrespitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usersearchrespitem/</guid><description>UserSearchRespItem Properties Name Type Description Notes user_id int The ID of the user. [optional] username str [optional]</description></item><item><title>UserSysAdminFlag</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usersysadminflag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/usersysadminflag/</guid><description>UserSysAdminFlag Properties Name Type Description Notes sysadmin_flag bool true-admin, false-not admin. [optional]</description></item><item><title>VulnerabilitySummary</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/vulnerabilitysummary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/vulnerabilitysummary/</guid><description>VulnerabilitySummary Properties Name Type Description Notes total int The total number of the found vulnerabilities [optional] fixable int The number of the fixable vulnerabilities [optional] summary dict(str, int) Numbers of the vulnerabilities with different severity [optional]</description></item><item><title>WebhookJob</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhookjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhookjob/</guid><description>WebhookJob Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The webhook job ID. [optional] policy_id int The webhook policy ID. [optional] event_type str The webhook job event type. [optional] notify_type str The webhook job notify type. [optional] status str The webhook job status. [optional] job_detail str The webhook job notify detailed data. [optional] creation_time datetime The webhook job creation time. [optional] update_time datetime The webhook job update time. [optional]</description></item><item><title>WebhookLastTrigger</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhooklasttrigger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhooklasttrigger/</guid><description>WebhookLastTrigger Properties Name Type Description Notes policy_name str The webhook policy name. [optional] event_type str The webhook event type. [optional] enabled bool Whether or not the webhook policy enabled. [optional] creation_time datetime The creation time of webhook policy. [optional] last_trigger_time datetime The last trigger time of webhook policy. [optional]</description></item><item><title>WebhookPolicy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhookpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhookpolicy/</guid><description>WebhookPolicy Properties Name Type Description Notes id int The webhook policy ID. [optional] name str The name of webhook policy. [optional] description str The description of webhook policy. [optional] project_id int The project ID of webhook policy. [optional] targets list[WebhookTargetObject] [optional] event_types list[str] [optional] creator str The creator of the webhook policy. [optional] creation_time datetime The create time of the webhook policy. [optional] update_time datetime The update time of the webhook policy.</description></item><item><title>WebhookTargetObject</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhooktargetobject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/webhooktargetobject/</guid><description>WebhookTargetObject Properties Name Type Description Notes type str The webhook target notify type. [optional] address str The webhook target address. [optional] auth_header str The webhook auth header. [optional] skip_cert_verify bool Whether or not to skip cert verify. [optional]</description></item><item><title>Worker</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/worker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/worker/</guid><description>Worker Properties Name Type Description Notes id str the id of the worker [optional] pool_id str the id of the worker pool [optional] job_name str the name of the running job in the worker [optional] job_id str the id of the running job in the worker [optional] start_at datetime The start time of the worker [optional] check_in str the checkin of the running job in the worker [optional] checkin_at datetime The checkin time of the worker [optional]</description></item><item><title>WorkerPool</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/workerpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/model/workerpool/</guid><description>WorkerPool Properties Name Type Description Notes pid int the process id of jobservice [optional] worker_pool_id str the id of the worker pool [optional] start_at datetime The start time of the work pool [optional] heartbeat_at datetime The heartbeat time of the work pool [optional] concurrency int The concurrency of the work pool [optional] host str The host of the work pool [optional]</description></item><item><title>Manage Pre-Installed Scanners</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/manage-pre-installed-scanners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/manage-pre-installed-scanners/</guid><description>Manage Pre-Installed Scanners You can find pre-installed vulnerability scanners under Administration -&amp;gt; Interrogation Services -&amp;gt; Scanners. If you click on an arrow next to a scanner, you&amp;rsquo;ll see the most important details about it. If you select a scanner using the small circle next to its name, you can perform the following actions with it
Set a Default Vulnerability Scanner Use the Set as Default button to set a new default scanner for your instance: Edit Existing Scanner Click on the Action button and then select Edit: That will open a dialogue window where you can change:</description></item><item><title>Registration for System Admins</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/registration-for-system-admins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/registration-for-system-admins/</guid><description>Registration for System Admins: Create a New Instance All accounts with a Dedicated Service subscription can have multiple users. For the first time, the system administrator must complete the subscription purchase and configure the instance to enable other users to work with it later.
Users of Individual accounts are considered system admins of their accounts. The registration is the same.
To start working with Container Registry:
Go to our pricing page; Select your subscription or start a free trial; Fill in the form and provide your credit card details; Check your emails: you must have received a confirmation that your account has been created; Inside the email, click on password to display your password; you will be re-directed to a single use secure URL generated by OneTimeSecret where you can see your password for the Container Registry account; INFO The password will be kept by OneTimeSecret for a while but try to finish the registration within a few hours.</description></item><item><title>UAA Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/uaa-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/uaa-authentication/</guid><description>UAA Authentication A user authentication and authorization server issues access tokens for your application to make it able to access another application: in this case, your Container Registry instance. You can configure a UAA server by yourself or select a provider that will set up for you a UAA instance. This instance will generate a token every time the user identity was confirmed  the user was authenticated  to enable user authorization that allows the user to perform certain actions in the system he was successfully logged in to.</description></item><item><title>Push and Pull Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/push-and-pull-images/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/push-and-pull-images/</guid><description>Push and Pull Images Pushing and pulling images is explained in detail in this getting started guide.</description></item><item><title>Tag Retention</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-retention/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-retention/</guid><description>Tag Retention As a project administrator, you can save storage capacity by defining rules to govern the number and retention period of artifacts stored in a repository. This allows you to keep only the necessary artifacts and discard those that are no longer required or have been superseded by a newer version. Managing your repository in this way can help ensure that only the most needed artifacts are kept, freeing up valuable storage space.</description></item><item><title>Artifact Page</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/artifact-page/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/artifact-page/</guid><description>Artifact Page When you click on a single artifact, you will be redirected to a view showing detailed information about this artifact. In this view, you can also perform a few additional actions on the selected artifact.
Tags Overview Working with tags is described in detail in another tutorial since the features for doing this are distributed across the GUI. The current section explains general GUI features that are available in the single artifact view.</description></item><item><title>Managing Project Users</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/managing-project-users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/managing-project-users/</guid><description>Managing Project Users The user that created a project and the super admin of the instance can add users to projects to enable them to perform different actions.
It is possible to pull images from a public repository without being a project member. But a membership grants users other rights depending on the role they are assigned.
Project Member Permissions Below is the overview of all project permissions by five types of roles:</description></item><item><title>New User Sign Up</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/new-user-sign-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/new-user-sign-up/</guid><description>New User Sign Up Container Registry is a cloud-based solution that you can use in your browser or CLI tool or through an API.
Your Instance on Container Registry All accounts with a Dedicated Service subscription receive a subdomain on container-registry.com. Your organization can also request a custom domain.
Every subdomain/domain represents one instance. For different instances, you need different login credentials.
Registration Methods As a user, you can use one of these methods to register in your Container Registry instance:</description></item><item><title>What Is Harbor?</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/what-is-harbor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/what-is-harbor/</guid><description>What Is Harbor? Our service is built upon Harbor. Harbor is an open-source technology for storing and managing container images. It was developed by VMware, a leading provider of virtual machines, and then transferred to the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), one of the biggest open-source initiatives.
In its turn, the Harbor project evolved out of Docker&amp;rsquo;s source code. Its contributors attempted to enhance the latter and eliminate its security problems.</description></item><item><title>Add New Scanners</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/add-new-scanners/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/add-new-scanners/</guid><description>Add New Scanners Although vulnerability scanning is a highly unified procedure, different scanners may capture different vulnerabilities. Some scanners are developed to act in a more severe way than others to meet specific compliance requirements. Nonetheless, adding more scanners may increase the general coverage and improve your cyber security.
To add a new scanner:
Expand Administration; Go to Interrogation Services; On the Scanners tab, click + New Scanner; Fill in the form: Give your scanner a name; Optionally, add a description; Enter the endpoint URL or IP address (if you are using an internal server); Choose your authorization method: For Basic one, enter your username and password which you received from the scanner provider; For Bearer, enter the secret token from your provider; For API key, enter the API key from your account on the scanner service provider.</description></item><item><title>LDAP/AD Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/ldap-ad-authentication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/ldap-ad-authentication/</guid><description>LDAP/AD Authentication Every company needs a directory where all user login data is kept. There are two popular technologies for configuring and managing such directories  Windows Active Directory (AD) and Lightweight Directory Access Protocol  that are Harbor-compatible. It means that you can use an LDAP/AD server to add new users to the Container Registry instance and manage existing accounts on the server.
Indeed, you need to set up and configure such a server before you can activate this kind of user authentication in Container Registry.</description></item><item><title>Tag Immutability</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-immutability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tags/tag-immutability/</guid><description>Tag Immutability What Is Tag Immutability and Why You Need It Harbor, the technology behind Container Registry, cannot (yet) deal with the situation when more than one image has the same tag. When there is an image in the registry with a certain tag, and then another image with the same tag is pushed to it, the first image loses its tag. The second image, pushed later, retains the tag but only until the next image with the same tag is pushed.</description></item><item><title>Working With Tags</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/working-with-tags/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/working-with-tags/</guid><description>Working With Tags Image tags have a function similar to those of the branch refs in Git: pointing to a state of the artifact at a specific time. Originally, the purpose of image tags was to differentiate between multiple versions of the same image. But more often than not different tags may refer to the same image.
The tags come in handy when you want to pull and run an image.</description></item><item><title>Push and Pull Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/push-and-pull-images/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/push-and-pull-images/</guid><description>Push and Pull Images Log In to Your Private Registry If you use a private registry, you need to use Docker login to push and pull images to and from Container Registry. For this, you can use your Container Registry username but you need to generate your CLI login for Docker first.
Go to your user profile in the upper right corner of the cockpit: Copy the CLI secret: In your command line tool, log in to Docker: docker login your-subdomain.</description></item><item><title>Container Registry User Interface: A Short Overview</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/container-registry-user-interface-a-short-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/container-registry-user-interface-a-short-overview/</guid><description>Container Registry User Interface: A Short Overview When you log in to your Container Registry account as a user, you will see the following console.
INFO If you log in as an administrator, you will see an additional administration section. Refer to our Administration Guide for the GUI features overview.
Main GUI Features The navigation pane provides you access to your projects and logs.
Projects are folders for your images which can be assigned certain settings.</description></item><item><title>OIDC Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/oidc-authentication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/oidc-authentication/</guid><description>OpenID Connect Single Sign-On Authentication We support all OIDC compliant identity providers. In the User Guides section, you can find selected configuration tutorials that explain how the settings look like on the provider side.
This reference, explains what you need to do in your Container Registry instance to enable and configure the OIDC login. Usually, you should proceed with this tutorial if you have access to your OIDC&amp;rsquo;s provider management console to set up new client.</description></item><item><title>Scanning Artifacts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/scanning-artifacts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/scanning-artifacts/</guid><description>Scanning Artifacts Read more about vulnerability scanning and how the health score is calculated here.
Running a System-Wide Scan As a system administrator, you can scan all artifacts in your instance at once.
Go to Administration; Click Interrogation Services; Select Vulnerability tab; Click Scan now. This will set the whole process in motion. You can watch the progress. Schedule a Scan Inside the vulnerability tab, you can schedule a system-wide scan.</description></item><item><title>User Management</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/user-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/user-management/</guid><description>User Management Add Another System Admin You can make another user a system admin:
In the navigation pane, expand the Administration section; Select Users; Select a user name from the list; Click SET AS ADMIN. The new admin will have the same rights as the existing ones.
Revoke System Admin Access To revoke admin access rights, repeat the steps from the previous section. Instead of Set as Admin, you will see REVOKE ADMIN after selecting user names.</description></item><item><title>Webhooks</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/webhooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/webhooks/</guid><description>Webhooks Webhooks are API push notifications sent in the form of HTTP or HHTPS POST requests. They pro-actively deliver messages to other applications when some event occurs inside their own application.
They can inform or trigger further events in the destination application. For instance, you can directly deploy an application upon the image push. This allows you to automate your deployments.
In Container Registry, you can add either an HTTP or Slack-based HTTPS URL that will be used for receiving the messages by the target application.</description></item><item><title>Other Useful Features</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/other-useful-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/other-useful-features/</guid><description>Other Useful Features Our Harbor-based cloud service allows you to manage your images easier. Apart from pulling and pushing images to and from your container registry, you can:
Facilitate your Kubernetes deployments by seamless integration between your Kubernetes clusters and Harbor-based container registries; using Kubernetes YAML manifests: Helm Charts; access your Chart Museum directly from the GUI Bypass connectivity issues by using a proxy cache: a pull-through cache for another target registry; a cached copy is checked against the target and is always up-to-date.</description></item><item><title>General Configurations</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/general-configurations/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/scanners/general-configurations/</guid><description>General Configurations System-Wide CVE Allowlist You can manage your deployment security by excluding certain vulnerabilities  entries in the Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures List  from the health score calculation. Project admins can do this on the project level re-using system-wide CVE lists or creating their own.
Add Items to a System-Wide CVE Allowlist In the navigation pane, expand Administration; Go to Configuration; Open System Settings; Scroll down to Deployment Security; Click ADD; Find the vulnerability in this database; Enter the items separated by simple commans or line breaks; Select an expiration date for the allowlist or click Never expires; Click ADD; Click Save.</description></item><item><title>System Robot Accounts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-robot-accounts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-robot-accounts/</guid><description>System Robot Accounts Robot accounts are used to let another application log in to Container Registry automatically.
The overview of all robot accounts in your instance is available from Navigation -&amp;gt; Robot Accounts.
Please note that all robot accounts get a prefix to their names when they are created. By default, the prefix is robot$. It is possible to configure another prefix as described here.
Available Robot Account Permissions Robot accounts can access Container Registry through API or a command line tool but never the GUI.</description></item><item><title>Endpoints For Replications and Proxy Cache</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/endpoints-for-replications-and-proxy-cache/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/endpoints-for-replications-and-proxy-cache/</guid><description>Endpoints For Replications and Proxy Cache Projects Endpoints are container image registries. They can be instances of the Container Registry platform, or other Harbor-based registries, or even non-Harbor-based ones.
Non-Harbor Registries: General Information Supported Non-Harbor Registries For Replications Ali Cloud Container Registry (Alibaba ACR); Artifact Hub; AWS Elastic Container Registry; Azure Container Registry; Docker Hub; Docker registry; DTR; GitHub GHCR; Gitlab; Google Container Registry; Harbor; Huawei SWR; Jfrog Artifactory; Quay; Tencent TCR.</description></item><item><title>Working With Logs</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/working-with-logs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/working-with-logs/</guid><description>Working With Logs Logs track everything that happens in your system. You can access logs from different places in the GUI.
Event Logs You will see this side bar on the right from everywhere in Container Registry. Hover over the EVENT LOG tab to exapnd it.
Event log includes high-level events, for instance, adding or deleting a new user to the system:
In some cases, project-related events will be also displayed in this section.</description></item><item><title>Configure Replication Rules</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/replication/configure-replication-rules/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/replication/configure-replication-rules/</guid><description>Configure Replication Rules Replication rules specify which artifacts will be moved between registries and how they should be moved. Each replication rule includes:
a filter to catch particular artifacts; a scheduler; a flattening rule. Create or Configure a Replication Rule Prerequisite You need at least one endpoint  a registry to push or pull images from  to create a new replication rule.
Steps In the navigation, select Administration and then Replications; Click + New Replication Rule; If you want to edit an existing one, select it for editing as explained below; Fill in the form: Name should not have any white spaces; Description is optional; Replication mode: Push-based means that you will push images from your current Container Registry instance into a remote one; Pull-based means that you will pull images to your current Container registry instance from a remote one; Resource filter: in the push replication mode, your current instance is the resource, whereas, in the pull mode, the resource is the remote registry; the resource filter selects which artifacts should be included in the replication: Name is the repository name; however, you can include all repositories by specifying in this field only the name of the project or using patterns; Tag is the artifact tag; Label; In the Resource dropdown, you can choose between the artifact type: chart, image, or any artifact.</description></item><item><title>System-Wide Labels</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-wide-labels/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-wide-labels/</guid><description>System-Wide Labels Labels are colored tags that can be added to artifacts and are only visible in the Container Registry GUI. They help you to find artifacts quickly since they can be used in some filters and since they are more eye-catchy than tags. They can be added on the project level by project administrators as explained here, but system administrators can also create system-wide labels that can be used for all projects.</description></item><item><title>Project Quotas</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/project-quotas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/project-quotas/</guid><description>Project Quotas Individual accounts have 1 GB of storage included. Dedicated accounts have 100 GB. You can set the upper limit for storage usage for every project.
Overview of the Storage Usage In the Project Quotas tab of the navigation pane, you can check how much storage is used and by which projects. Default disk space per project shows how much storage every newly created project will be assigned. The bar in the Storage column of the overview shows the percentage of storage use.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Individual Account</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/dedicated-vs-individual-account/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/dedicated-vs-individual-account/</guid><description>Dedicated vs Individual Account Container Registry offers three types of pricing plans:
individual; dedicated; custom/enterprise. The present documentation is mostly written with dedicated accounts in mind. We would like to explain the differences between the three. The table below summarizes critical distinctions. You can also refer to our pricing page.
Position Individual Dedicated Custom Tenants 1 tenant Multitenancy Multitenancy Repositores Only private Private and public Private and public Domain c8n.io Subdomain on container-registry.</description></item><item><title>Double-Starred Patterns</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/double-starred-patterns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/double-starred-patterns/</guid><description>Double-Starred Patterns Some Container Registry GUI features allow you to use string matching instead of entering complete names of repositories or tags. That comes in handy if you create separate repositories or tags for every stage in the software development lifecycle and follow a naming convention. In this case, you can select more than one repository or tag by typing in only the pattern once instead of listing all their names.</description></item><item><title>Terminal Deletion of Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/terminal-deletion-of-images/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/terminal-deletion-of-images/</guid><description>Terminal Deletion of Images: Garbage Collection A simple delete operation is not enough to remove images  to be precise, their blob files  from the system. When you use a delete button on the artifacts overview page inside a repository, it simply deletes the corresponding item from the GUI. It means that simple deletion does not clean up your storage, and you may be hitting your project quotas even if you do not see a lot of artifacts in there.</description></item><item><title>Other System Settings</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/other-system-settings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/other-system-settings/</guid><description>Other System Settings Under Administration -&amp;gt; Configuration -&amp;gt; System Settings you will find a few more system-wide settings. Project Authorship In the dropdown Project Creation, you can specify who can create new projects in your instance. You have a choice between system admins and all other users.
Token Expiration You need a token every time you want to login into your private registry from Docker. You can specify how many minutes it is valid.</description></item><item><title>Proxy Cache Projects</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/proxy-cache-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/proxy-cache-projects/</guid><description>Proxy Cache Projects Why Use Container Registry as a Proxy Cache Container Registry can be used as a proxy cache for images originally stored on Docker Hub.
There are a few reasons why you would avoid pulling images from Docker Hub directly.
Docker Rate Limit Docker Hub has a download limit rate which is defined differently for different subscription plans. In our blog post, we explain why you can hit the limits quite quickly and which consequences it may have for your workflows.</description></item><item><title>How to automate Flask development workflow with Container Registry and GitHub Actions</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/how-to-automate-flask-development-workflow-with-container-registry-and-github-actions/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/how-to-automate-flask-development-workflow-with-container-registry-and-github-actions/</guid><description>In this tutorial, we will develop an automated workflow to build a containerized Flask application.
This workflow will build a new container image every time a new commit is pushed to our GitHub repository. We will be using a simple Flask application for this tutorial. But you can use this workflow to build a Flask application of any complexity.
We will run the workflow with GitHub Actions and use 8gears Container Registry as our image repository.</description></item><item><title>KubeCon North America 2023  The Takeaways</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/2023-kubecon-chicago-takeaways/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/2023-kubecon-chicago-takeaways/</guid><description>&lt;p>This year&amp;rsquo;s North America edition of the KubeCon took place in Chicago. What a
beautiful city. As someone who only experienced the United States through
movies, it felt a bit surreal at first, because around each corner or location I
felt like I had seen this exact scene in a movie.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How Does Dockers Decision of Sunsetting Free Team Organizations Impacts You</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/how-does-dockers-decision-of-sunsetting-free-team-organizations-impacts-you/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/how-does-dockers-decision-of-sunsetting-free-team-organizations-impacts-you/</guid><description>&lt;p>Docker Inc. continues on its course of eliminating free offerings: Now the &amp;ldquo;Docker Free Team&amp;rdquo; model
has to take its turn. With the Free Team Organizations offering, it was possible to publish public
container images for free in Docker Hub. Many open-source projects have taken advantage of the offer;
however, the impact is affecting everyone.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>What's new in Harbor 2.6</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/whats-new-in-harbor-version-2.6.0/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/whats-new-in-harbor-version-2.6.0/</guid><description>&lt;p>Harbor 2.6 is about to land in the next days containing some long-awaited functionalities and two important deprecations.
With over 150 enhancements and bug fixes, this release further improves stability and reliability.
The deprecation hits Notary and ChartMuseum, which was used in Harbor to store Helm Chart Repositories.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Meet with Vadim from Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/contact/vadim/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/contact/vadim/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Container Image Versioning</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/container-image-versioning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/container-image-versioning/</guid><description>&lt;p>Containers have simplified how we develop and deploy software. The way in which container images are managed is a critical component of a smooth CI/CD process. Container Registries act as trusted intermediaries between development and runtime environments for containerized applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/getting-started-with-harbor-container-registry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/getting-started-with-harbor-container-registry/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ready to push the image to a registry? In this post, we will discuss how to get started with Container Registry.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Harbor Release 2.2.0</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/harbor-2.2.0-new-features-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/harbor-2.2.0-new-features-explained/</guid><description>&lt;p>Harbor 2.2.0 was just released and comes with some very interesting features.
This post walks you through the newly added features and changes explaining the capabilities. Since the last release of v2.1.0 in September 2020, eleven contributors made 41 changes and resolved 189 issues.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Error</title><link>https://container-registry.com/aws/error/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/aws/error/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Subscription Success</title><link>https://container-registry.com/subscription/success/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/subscription/success/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s Next? As you can see, we already started the setup process and within a few minutes, you will receive:
A welcome email with the URL and credentials to your new container registry Order confirmation email from our subscription management system While you are waiting In the meantime, you can check out the following resources:
Blog Frequently Asked Questions Improve your containerized workflow Help Support Chat is the best way to contact us for real-time support and technical problems.</description></item><item><title>Distributing Commercial Software Through Container Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/distributing-commercial-software-through-container-images/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/distributing-commercial-software-through-container-images/</guid><description>&lt;p>When delivering software to clients, many independent software vendors (ISVs) still rely on methods involving traditional software packaging methods such as downloadable binaries, ZIPs, or other type of compressed delivery. These distribution approaches are often OS specific. As a result, developers are forced to spend precious time on tailoring software delivery rather than innovation. Containerization is already simplifying software delivery for many of today&amp;rsquo;s mainstream products. Choosing the right &lt;a href="https://container-registry.com">container registry that meets ISVs requirements&lt;/a> is crucial to satisfy vendors and meet client expectations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifting Developers Productivity with BuildKit CLI for kubectl</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/productivity-lift-buildkit-cli-for-kubectl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/productivity-lift-buildkit-cli-for-kubectl/</guid><description>&lt;p>Developing and testing software on Kubernetes usually means building and moving container images from the developer workstation to a container registry, and ultimately, Kubernetes. When considering all the moving parts, the complexity and context switches break the development flow. Gone are the days where developers just hit a command and a few seconds later the newly built software is ready for testing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What if there was some magical tool that you could simply feed instructions like: &amp;ldquo;Build this Dockerfile &lt;em>here&lt;/em> and replace any existing image on &lt;em>that&lt;/em> Kubernetes cluster with the results!&amp;rdquo; ASAP. Spoiler Alert! That is exactly what BuildKit CLI for kubectl is there to do.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>3 Ways to overcome the Docker Hub pull rate limit</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</guid><description>&lt;p>As someone who is working with Docker Container images, you are here for one of the following reasons:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>You came across the new Docker Hub pull rate limit;&lt;/li>
&lt;li>You encountered the error message &lt;code>You have reached your pull rate limit&lt;/code>
Anyway, you are now desperate to find a solution.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Container Registry Terms of Service</title><link>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</guid><description>Container Registry Terms of Service Effective as of: November 1, 2020
These Container Registry Terms of Service (these &amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) apply to the features and functions provided by 8gears Ltd.(&amp;ldquo;8gears,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) via container-registry.com, private-docker-registry.com, c8n.io and c8n.me (the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;, collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;).
By accessing or using the Services, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, do not use any of the Services.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://container-registry.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/about/</guid><description>Container Registry started out in 2016 as a Portus Powered Container Registry Service for teams and organizations. In September 2020 we switched the software stack to Harbor as the new foundation to better support cloud native and multi cloud workloads.
Our Background Many solutions arise from their own and immediate needs. We were building a new microservice-based software stack for a new project and faced for the second time in a row the difficulty to find a decent Docker Registry suitable for teams and organizations.</description></item><item><title>ArtifactApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/artifactapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/artifactapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ArtifactApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description add_label POST /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/labels Add label to artifact copy_artifact POST /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts Copy artifact create_tag POST /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/tags Create tag delete_artifact DELETE /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference} Delete the specific artifact delete_tag DELETE /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/tags/{tag_name} Delete tag get_addition GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/additions/{addition} Get the addition of the specific artifact get_artifact GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference} Get the specific artifact get_vulnerabilities_addition GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/additions/vulnerabilities Get the vulnerabilities addition of the specific artifact list_accessories GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/accessories List accessories list_artifacts GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts List artifacts list_tags GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/tags List tags remove_label DELETE /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/labels/{label_id} Remove label from artifact add_label Signature add_label(project_name: str, repository_name: str, reference: str, label: Label, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Add label to artifact</description></item><item><title>AuditlogApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/auditlogapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/auditlogapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.AuditlogApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description list_audit_logs GET /audit-logs Get recent logs of the projects which the user is a member of list_audit_logs Signature list_audit_logs(x_request_id: Optional[str], q: Optional[str], sort: Optional[str], page: Optional[int], page_size: Optional[int])-&amp;gt; list[AuditLog] Get recent logs of the projects which the user is a member of
This endpoint let user see the recent operation logs of the projects which he is member of</description></item><item><title>ConfigureApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/configureapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/configureapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ConfigureApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_configurations GET /configurations Get system configurations. get_internalconfig GET /internalconfig Get internal configurations. update_configurations PUT /configurations Modify system configurations. get_configurations Signature get_configurations(x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; ConfigurationsResponse Get system configurations.
This endpoint is for retrieving system configurations that only provides for admin user.
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>Containerized Software Distribution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/containerized-software-distribution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/containerized-software-distribution/</guid><description>Containerized Software Distribution For software vendors who want to avoid the Wild West of environmental variations of their customers.
Delivering Your Software Distribute your software to customers as container images, giving them a convenient way to use your containerized software. You have complete control over your customers access and duration to your container images. Connect your software access to a paid membership or integrate it into your CRM, ERP, Analytics, or other system.</description></item><item><title>GcApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/gcapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/gcapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.GcApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_gc_schedule POST /system/gc/schedule Create a gc schedule. get_gc GET /system/gc/{gc_id} Get gc status. get_gc_history GET /system/gc Get gc results. get_gc_log GET /system/gc/{gc_id}/log Get gc job log. get_gc_schedule GET /system/gc/schedule Get gc's schedule. stop_gc PUT /system/gc/{gc_id} Stop the specific GC execution update_gc_schedule PUT /system/gc/schedule Update gc's schedule. create_gc_schedule Signature create_gc_schedule(schedule: Schedule, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Create a gc schedule.
This endpoint is for update gc schedule.</description></item><item><title>HealthApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/healthapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/healthapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.HealthApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_health GET /health Check the status of Harbor components get_health Signature get_health(x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; OverallHealthStatus Check the status of Harbor components
Check the status of Harbor components
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.Configuration() configuration.username = &amp;#39;YOUR_USERNAME&amp;#39; configuration.password = &amp;#39;YOUR_PASSWORD&amp;#39; # create an instance of the API class api_instance = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>IconApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/iconapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/iconapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.IconApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_icon GET /icons/{digest} Get artifact icon get_icon Signature get_icon(digest: str, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; Icon Get artifact icon
Get the artifact icon with the specified digest. As the original icon image is resized and encoded before returning, the parameter &amp;quot;digest&amp;quot; in the path doesn&amp;rsquo;t match the hash of the returned content
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>ImmutableApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/immutableapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/immutableapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ImmutableApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_immu_rule POST /projects/{project_name_or_id}/immutabletagrules Add an immutable tag rule to current project delete_immu_rule DELETE /projects/{project_name_or_id}/immutabletagrules/{immutable_rule_id} Delete the immutable tag rule. list_immu_rules GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/immutabletagrules List all immutable tag rules of current project update_immu_rule PUT /projects/{project_name_or_id}/immutabletagrules/{immutable_rule_id} Update the immutable tag rule or enable or disable the rule create_immu_rule Signature create_immu_rule(project_name_or_id: str, immutable_rule: ImmutableRule, x_request_id: Optional[str], x_is_resource_name: Optional[bool])-&amp;gt; None Add an immutable tag rule to current project</description></item><item><title>Improve your containerized workflow</title><link>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</guid><description>Improve Your Containerized Image Management Meet our experts for a free and individual session on how to improve your containerized workflow.</description></item><item><title>JobserviceApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/jobserviceapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/jobserviceapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.JobserviceApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description action_pending_jobs PUT /jobservice/queues/{job_type} stop and clean, pause, resume pending jobs in the queue get_worker_pools GET /jobservice/pools Get worker pools get_workers GET /jobservice/pools/{pool_id}/workers Get workers list_job_queues GET /jobservice/queues list job queues stop_running_job PUT /jobservice/jobs/{job_id} Stop running job action_pending_jobs Signature action_pending_jobs(job_type: str, action_request: ActionRequest, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None stop and clean, pause, resume pending jobs in the queue
stop and clean, pause, resume pending jobs in the queue</description></item><item><title>LabelApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/labelapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/labelapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.LabelApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_label POST /labels Post creates a label delete_label DELETE /labels/{label_id} Delete the label specified by ID. get_label_by_id GET /labels/{label_id} Get the label specified by ID. list_labels GET /labels List labels according to the query strings. update_label PUT /labels/{label_id} Update the label properties. create_label Signature create_label(label: Label, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Post creates a label
This endpoint let user creates a label.</description></item><item><title>LdapApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/ldapapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/ldapapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.LdapApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description import_ldap_user POST /ldap/users/import Import selected available ldap users. ping_ldap POST /ldap/ping Ping available ldap service. search_ldap_group GET /ldap/groups/search Search available ldap groups. search_ldap_user GET /ldap/users/search Search available ldap users. import_ldap_user Signature import_ldap_user(uid_list: LdapImportUsers, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Import selected available ldap users.
This endpoint adds the selected available ldap users to harbor based on related configuration parameters from the system. System will try to guess the user email address and realname, add to harbor user information.</description></item><item><title>MemberApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/memberapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/memberapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.MemberApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_project_member POST /projects/{project_name_or_id}/members Create project member delete_project_member DELETE /projects/{project_name_or_id}/members/{mid} Delete project member get_project_member GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/members/{mid} Get the project member information list_project_members GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/members Get all project member information update_project_member PUT /projects/{project_name_or_id}/members/{mid} Update project member create_project_member Signature create_project_member(project_name_or_id: str, x_request_id: Optional[str], x_is_resource_name: Optional[bool], project_member: Optional[ProjectMember])-&amp;gt; None Create project member
Create project member relationship, the member can be one of the user_member and group_member, The user_member need to specify user_id or username.</description></item><item><title>OidcApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/oidcapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/oidcapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.OidcApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description ping_oidc POST /system/oidc/ping Test the OIDC endpoint. ping_oidc Signature ping_oidc(endpoint: Endpoint, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Test the OIDC endpoint.
Test the OIDC endpoint, the setting of the endpoint is provided in the request. This API can only be called by system admin.
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>PingApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/pingapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/pingapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.PingApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_ping GET /ping Ping Harbor to check if it's alive. get_ping Signature get_ping(x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; str Ping Harbor to check if it&amp;rsquo;s alive.
This API simply replies a pong to indicate the process to handle API is up, disregarding the health status of dependent components.
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>PreheatApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/preheatapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/preheatapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.PreheatApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_instance POST /p2p/preheat/instances Create p2p provider instances create_policy POST /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies Create a preheat policy under a project delete_instance DELETE /p2p/preheat/instances/{preheat_instance_name} Delete the specified P2P provider instance delete_policy DELETE /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies/{preheat_policy_name} Delete a preheat policy get_execution GET /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies/{preheat_policy_name}/executions/{execution_id} Get a execution detail by id get_instance GET /p2p/preheat/instances/{preheat_instance_name} Get a P2P provider instance get_policy GET /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies/{preheat_policy_name} Get a preheat policy get_preheat_log GET /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies/{preheat_policy_name}/executions/{execution_id}/tasks/{task_id}/logs Get the log text stream of the specified task for the given execution list_executions GET /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies/{preheat_policy_name}/executions List executions for the given policy list_instances GET /p2p/preheat/instances List P2P provider instances list_policies GET /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies List preheat policies list_providers GET /p2p/preheat/providers List P2P providers list_providers_under_project GET /projects/{project_name}/preheat/providers Get all providers at project level list_tasks GET /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies/{preheat_policy_name}/executions/{execution_id}/tasks List all the related tasks for the given execution manual_preheat POST /projects/{project_name}/preheat/policies/{preheat_policy_name} Manual preheat ping_instances POST /p2p/preheat/instances/ping Ping status of a instance.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy of Container Registry Effective as of: November 1, 2020
Container Registry collects some Personal Data from its Users.
This document can be printed for reference by using the print command in the settings of any browser.
Our Privacy Policy at a Glance This is a condensed overview of the Personal Data we collect for the following purposes and using the following services:
Owner and Data Controller 8gears Ltd.</description></item><item><title>ProjectApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/projectapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/projectapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ProjectApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_project POST /projects Create a new project. delete_project DELETE /projects/{project_name_or_id} Delete project by projectID get_logs GET /projects/{project_name}/logs Get recent logs of the projects get_project GET /projects/{project_name_or_id} Return specific project detail information get_project_deletable GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/_deletable Get the deletable status of the project get_project_summary GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/summary Get summary of the project. get_scanner_of_project GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/scanner Get project level scanner head_project HEAD /projects Check if the project name user provided already exists.</description></item><item><title>ProjectMetadataApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/projectmetadataapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/projectmetadataapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ProjectMetadataApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description add_project_metadatas POST /projects/{project_name_or_id}/metadatas/ Add metadata for the specific project delete_project_metadata DELETE /projects/{project_name_or_id}/metadatas/{meta_name} Delete the specific metadata for the specific project get_project_metadata GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/metadatas/{meta_name} Get the specific metadata of the specific project list_project_metadatas GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/metadatas/ Get the metadata of the specific project update_project_metadata PUT /projects/{project_name_or_id}/metadatas/{meta_name} Update the specific metadata for the specific project add_project_metadatas Signature add_project_metadatas(project_name_or_id: str, x_request_id: Optional[str], x_is_resource_name: Optional[bool], metadata: Optional[object])-&amp;gt; None Add metadata for the specific project</description></item><item><title>PurgeApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/purgeapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/purgeapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.PurgeApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_purge_schedule POST /system/purgeaudit/schedule Create a purge job schedule. get_purge_history GET /system/purgeaudit Get purge job results. get_purge_job GET /system/purgeaudit/{purge_id} Get purge job status. get_purge_job_log GET /system/purgeaudit/{purge_id}/log Get purge job log. get_purge_schedule GET /system/purgeaudit/schedule Get purge's schedule. stop_purge PUT /system/purgeaudit/{purge_id} Stop the specific purge audit log execution update_purge_schedule PUT /system/purgeaudit/schedule Update purge job's schedule. create_purge_schedule Signature create_purge_schedule(schedule: Schedule, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Create a purge job schedule.</description></item><item><title>QuotaApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/quotaapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/quotaapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.QuotaApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_quota GET /quotas/{id} Get the specified quota list_quotas GET /quotas List quotas update_quota PUT /quotas/{id} Update the specified quota get_quota Signature get_quota(id: int, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; Quota Get the specified quota
Get the specified quota
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>RegistryApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/registryapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/registryapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.RegistryApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_registry POST /registries Create a registry delete_registry DELETE /registries/{id} Delete the specific registry get_registry GET /registries/{id} Get the specific registry get_registry_info GET /registries/{id}/info Get the registry info list_registries GET /registries List the registries list_registry_provider_infos GET /replication/adapterinfos List all registered registry provider information list_registry_provider_types GET /replication/adapters List registry adapters ping_registry POST /registries/ping Check status of a registry update_registry PUT /registries/{id} Update the registry create_registry Signature create_registry(registry: Registry, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Create a registry</description></item><item><title>ReplicationApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/replicationapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/replicationapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ReplicationApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_replication_policy POST /replication/policies Create a replication policy delete_replication_policy DELETE /replication/policies/{id} Delete the specific replication policy get_replication_execution GET /replication/executions/{id} Get the specific replication execution get_replication_log GET /replication/executions/{id}/tasks/{task_id}/log Get the log of the specific replication task get_replication_policy GET /replication/policies/{id} Get the specific replication policy list_replication_executions GET /replication/executions List replication executions list_replication_policies GET /replication/policies List replication policies list_replication_tasks GET /replication/executions/{id}/tasks List replication tasks for a specific execution start_replication POST /replication/executions Start one replication execution stop_replication PUT /replication/executions/{id} Stop the specific replication execution update_replication_policy PUT /replication/policies/{id} Update the replication policy create_replication_policy Signature create_replication_policy(policy: ReplicationPolicy, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Create a replication policy</description></item><item><title>RepositoryApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/repositoryapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/repositoryapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.RepositoryApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description delete_repository DELETE /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name} Delete repository get_repository GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name} Get repository list_all_repositories GET /repositories List all authorized repositories list_repositories GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories List repositories update_repository PUT /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name} Update repository delete_repository Signature delete_repository(project_name: str, repository_name: str, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Delete repository
Delete the repository specified by name
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>RetentionApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/retentionapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/retentionapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.RetentionApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_retention POST /retentions Create Retention Policy delete_retention DELETE /retentions/{id} Delete Retention Policy get_rentenition_metadata GET /retentions/metadatas Get Retention Metadatas get_retention GET /retentions/{id} Get Retention Policy get_retention_task_log GET /retentions/{id}/executions/{eid}/tasks/{tid} Get Retention job task log list_retention_executions GET /retentions/{id}/executions Get Retention executions list_retention_tasks GET /retentions/{id}/executions/{eid}/tasks Get Retention tasks operate_retention_execution PATCH /retentions/{id}/executions/{eid} Stop a Retention execution trigger_retention_execution POST /retentions/{id}/executions Trigger a Retention Execution update_retention PUT /retentions/{id} Update Retention Policy create_retention Signature create_retention(policy: RetentionPolicy, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Create Retention Policy</description></item><item><title>RobotApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/robotapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/robotapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.RobotApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_robot POST /robots Create a robot account delete_robot DELETE /robots/{robot_id} Delete a robot account get_robot_by_id GET /robots/{robot_id} Get a robot account list_robot GET /robots Get robot account refresh_sec PATCH /robots/{robot_id} Refresh the robot secret update_robot PUT /robots/{robot_id} Update a robot account create_robot Signature create_robot(robot: RobotCreate, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; RobotCreated Create a robot account
Create a robot account
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>Robotv1Api</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/robotv1api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/robotv1api/</guid><description>harbor_client.Robotv1Api All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_robot_v1 POST /projects/{project_name_or_id}/robots Create a robot account delete_robot_v1 DELETE /projects/{project_name_or_id}/robots/{robot_id} Delete a robot account get_robot_by_idv1 GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/robots/{robot_id} Get a robot account list_robot_v1 GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/robots Get all robot accounts of specified project update_robot_v1 PUT /projects/{project_name_or_id}/robots/{robot_id} Update status of robot account. create_robot_v1 Signature create_robot_v1(project_name_or_id: str, robot: RobotCreateV1, x_request_id: Optional[str], x_is_resource_name: Optional[bool])-&amp;gt; RobotCreated Create a robot account
Create a robot account
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>ScanAllApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scanallapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scanallapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ScanAllApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_scan_all_schedule POST /system/scanAll/schedule Create a schedule or a manual trigger for the scan all job. get_latest_scan_all_metrics GET /scans/all/metrics Get the metrics of the latest scan all process get_latest_scheduled_scan_all_metrics GET /scans/schedule/metrics Get the metrics of the latest scheduled scan all process get_scan_all_schedule GET /system/scanAll/schedule Get scan all's schedule. stop_scan_all POST /system/scanAll/stop Stop scanAll job execution update_scan_all_schedule PUT /system/scanAll/schedule Update scan all's schedule.</description></item><item><title>ScanApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scanapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scanapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ScanApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_report_log GET /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/scan/{report_id}/log Get the log of the scan report scan_artifact POST /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/scan Scan the artifact stop_scan_artifact POST /projects/{project_name}/repositories/{repository_name}/artifacts/{reference}/scan/stop Cancelling a scan job for a particular artifact get_report_log Signature get_report_log(project_name: str, repository_name: str, reference: str, report_id: str, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; str Get the log of the scan report
Get the log of the scan report
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>ScanDataExportApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scandataexportapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scandataexportapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ScanDataExportApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description download_scan_data GET /export/cve/download/{execution_id} Download the scan data export file export_scan_data POST /export/cve Export scan data for selected projects get_scan_data_export_execution GET /export/cve/execution/{execution_id} Get the specific scan data export execution get_scan_data_export_execution_list GET /export/cve/executions Get a list of specific scan data export execution jobs for a specified user download_scan_data Signature download_scan_data(execution_id: int, x_request_id: Optional[str], format: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; str Download the scan data export file</description></item><item><title>ScannerApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scannerapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scannerapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ScannerApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_scanner POST /scanners Create a scanner registration delete_scanner DELETE /scanners/{registration_id} Delete a scanner registration get_scanner GET /scanners/{registration_id} Get a scanner registration details get_scanner_metadata GET /scanners/{registration_id}/metadata Get the metadata of the specified scanner registration list_scanners GET /scanners List scanner registrations ping_scanner POST /scanners/ping Tests scanner registration settings set_scanner_as_default PATCH /scanners/{registration_id} Set system default scanner registration update_scanner PUT /scanners/{registration_id} Update a scanner registration create_scanner Signature create_scanner(registration: ScannerRegistrationReq, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; None Create a scanner registration</description></item><item><title>ScheduleApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scheduleapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/scheduleapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.ScheduleApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_schedule_paused GET /schedules/{job_type}/paused list_schedules GET /schedules get_schedule_paused Signature get_schedule_paused(job_type: str, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; SchedulerStatus Get scheduler paused status
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.Configuration() configuration.username = &amp;#39;YOUR_USERNAME&amp;#39; configuration.password = &amp;#39;YOUR_PASSWORD&amp;#39; # create an instance of the API class api_instance = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>SearchApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/searchapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/searchapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.SearchApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description search GET /search Search for projects, repositories and helm charts search Signature search(q: str, x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; Search Search for projects, repositories and helm charts
The Search endpoint returns information about the projects, repositories and helm charts offered at public status or related to the current logged in user. The response includes the project, repository list and charts in a proper display order.</description></item><item><title>StatisticApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/statisticapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/statisticapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.StatisticApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_statistic GET /statistics Get the statistic information about the projects and repositories get_statistic Signature get_statistic(x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; Statistic Get the statistic information about the projects and repositories
Get the statistic information about the projects and repositories
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>SystemCVEAllowlistApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/systemcveallowlistapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/systemcveallowlistapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.SystemCVEAllowlistApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_system_cve_allowlist GET /system/CVEAllowlist Get the system level allowlist of CVE. put_system_cve_allowlist PUT /system/CVEAllowlist Update the system level allowlist of CVE. get_system_cve_allowlist Signature get_system_cve_allowlist(x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; CVEAllowlist Get the system level allowlist of CVE.
Get the system level allowlist of CVE. This API can be called by all authenticated users.
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>SysteminfoApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/systeminfoapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/systeminfoapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.SysteminfoApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description get_cert GET /systeminfo/getcert Get default root certificate. get_system_info GET /systeminfo Get general system info get_volumes GET /systeminfo/volumes Get system volume info (total/free size). get_cert Signature get_cert(x_request_id: Optional[str])-&amp;gt; str Get default root certificate.
This endpoint is for downloading a default root certificate.
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>Technical Support</title><link>https://container-registry.com/contact/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/contact/support/</guid><description>Technical Support Get in touch with our live technical support.</description></item><item><title>UserApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/userapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/userapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.UserApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_user POST /users Create a local user. delete_user DELETE /users/{user_id} Mark a registered user as be removed. get_current_user_info GET /users/current Get current user info. get_current_user_permissions GET /users/current/permissions Get current user permissions. get_user GET /users/{user_id} Get a user's profile. list_users GET /users List users search_users GET /users/search Search users by username set_cli_secret PUT /users/{user_id}/cli_secret Set CLI secret for a user. set_user_sys_admin PUT /users/{user_id}/sysadmin Update a registered user to change to be an administrator of Harbor.</description></item><item><title>UsergroupApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/usergroupapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/usergroupapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.UsergroupApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_user_group POST /usergroups Create user group delete_user_group DELETE /usergroups/{group_id} Delete user group get_user_group GET /usergroups/{group_id} Get user group information list_user_groups GET /usergroups Get all user groups information search_user_groups GET /usergroups/search Search groups by groupname update_user_group PUT /usergroups/{group_id} Update group information create_user_group Signature create_user_group(x_request_id: Optional[str], usergroup: Optional[UserGroup])-&amp;gt; None Create user group
Create user group information
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.</description></item><item><title>WebhookApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/webhookapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/webhookapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.WebhookApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description create_webhook_policy_of_project POST /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/policies Create project webhook policy. delete_webhook_policy_of_project DELETE /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/policies/{webhook_policy_id} Delete webhook policy of a project get_supported_event_types GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/events Get supported event types and notify types. get_webhook_policy_of_project GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/policies/{webhook_policy_id} Get project webhook policy last_trigger GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/lasttrigger Get project webhook policy last trigger info list_webhook_policies_of_project GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/policies List project webhook policies. update_webhook_policy_of_project PUT /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/policies/{webhook_policy_id} Update webhook policy of a project. create_webhook_policy_of_project Signature create_webhook_policy_of_project(project_name_or_id: str, policy: WebhookPolicy, x_request_id: Optional[str], x_is_resource_name: Optional[bool])-&amp;gt; None Create project webhook policy.</description></item><item><title>WebhookjobApi</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/webhookjobapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/harbor-api-client/api/webhookjobapi/</guid><description>harbor_client.WebhookjobApi All URIs are relative to http://localhost/api/v2.0
Method HTTP request Description list_webhook_jobs GET /projects/{project_name_or_id}/webhook/jobs List project webhook jobs list_webhook_jobs Signature list_webhook_jobs(project_name_or_id: str, policy_id: int, x_request_id: Optional[str], x_is_resource_name: Optional[bool], q: Optional[str], sort: Optional[str], page: Optional[int], page_size: Optional[int], status: Optional[list[str]])-&amp;gt; list[WebhookJob] List project webhook jobs
This endpoint returns webhook jobs of a project.
Example from __future__ import print_function import time import harbor_client from harbor_client.rest import ApiException from pprint import pprint # Configure HTTP basic authorization: basic configuration = harbor_client.</description></item></channel></rss>