<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/</link><description>Recent content in Dedicated Container Registry as a Service on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started with Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/getting-started-with-harbor-container-registry/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/getting-started-with-harbor-container-registry/</guid><description>&lt;p>Ready to push the image to a registry? In this post, we will discuss how to get started with Container Registry.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Harbor Release 2.2.0</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/harbor-2.2.0-new-features-explained/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/harbor-2.2.0-new-features-explained/</guid><description>&lt;p>Harbor 2.2.0 was just released and comes with some very interesting features.
This post walks you through the newly added features and changes explaining the capabilities. Since the last release of v2.1.0 in September 2020, eleven contributors made 41 changes and resolved 189 issues.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Subscription Success</title><link>https://container-registry.com/subscription/success/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/subscription/success/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s Next? As you can see, we already started the setup process and within a few minutes, you will receive:
A welcome email with the URL and credentials to your new container registry Order confirmation email from our subscription management system While you ar waiting In the meantime, you can check out the following resources:
Blog Frequently Asked Questions Improve your containerized workflow Help Support Chat is the best way to contact us for real-time support and technical problems.</description></item><item><title>Distributing Commercial Software Through Container Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/distributing-commercial-software-through-container-images/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/distributing-commercial-software-through-container-images/</guid><description>&lt;p>When delivering software to clients, many independent software vendors (ISVs) still rely on methods involving traditional software packaging methods such as downloadable binaries, ZIPs, or other type of compressed delivery. These distribution approaches are often OS specific. As a result, developers are forced to spend precious time on tailoring software delivery rather than innovation. Containerization is already simplifying software delivery for many of today&amp;rsquo;s mainstream products. Choosing the right &lt;a href="https://container-registry.com">container registry that meets ISVs requirements&lt;/a> is crucial to satisfy vendors and meet client expectations.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lifting Developers’ Productivity with BuildKit CLI for kubectl</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/productivity-lift-buildkit-cli-for-kubectl/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/productivity-lift-buildkit-cli-for-kubectl/</guid><description>&lt;p>Developing and testing software on Kubernetes usually means building and moving container images from the developer workstation to a container registry, and ultimately, Kubernetes. When considering all the moving parts, the complexity and context switches break the development flow. Gone are the days where developers just hit a command and a few seconds later the newly built software is ready for testing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What if there was some magical tool that you could simply feed instructions like: &amp;ldquo;Build this Dockerfile &lt;em>here&lt;/em> and replace any existing image on &lt;em>that&lt;/em> Kubernetes cluster with the results!&amp;rdquo; ASAP. Spoiler Alert! That is exactly what BuildKit CLI for kubectl is there to do.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>3 Ways to overcome the Docker Hub pull rate limit</title><link>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/posts/overcome-docker-hub-rate-limit/</guid><description>&lt;p>As someone who is working with Docker Container images, you came across the new Docker Hub pull rate limit or perhaps you are already here because you encountered the error message &lt;code>You have reached your pull rate limit&lt;/code> and are now looking for a solution on how to resolve it.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Container Registry Terms of Service</title><link>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/terms-of-service/</guid><description>Container Registry Terms of Service Effective as of: November 1, 2020
These Container Registry Terms of Service (these &amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) apply to the features and functions provided by 8gears Ltd.(&amp;ldquo;8gears,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;our,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;) via container-registry.com, private-docker-registry.com, c8n.io and c8n.me (the &amp;ldquo;Site&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Service&amp;rdquo;, collectively, the &amp;ldquo;Services&amp;rdquo;).
By accessing or using the Services, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you do not agree to these Terms, do not use any of the Services.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://container-registry.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/about/</guid><description>Container Registry started out in 2016 as a Portus Powered Container Registry Service for teams and organizations. In September 2020 we switched our foundation from Portus to Harbor, to better serve those that mean the most to us, our customers.
Background Many solutions arise from their own and immediate needs. After we started a new container-centric consulting project and faced difficulties to find a decent alternative Docker Registry for the organization we were building, we merged into a microservice-based software.</description></item><item><title>Containerized Software Distribution</title><link>https://container-registry.com/containerized-software-distribution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/containerized-software-distribution/</guid><description>Distributing Commercial Software Through Container Images Distribute your software as a Docker Container. Give your customers a straightforward way to use your Containerized Software. Manage and automate customer access as wells as the access duration to container images. Link container images access to paid subscription plan. The possibilities are endless.
Offer Safe and secure Dedicated Container Registry Your branding with a custom domain Not Yet Convinced? Write us, chat with us or give us a call for an individual consultation.</description></item><item><title>Improve your containerized workflow</title><link>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/contact/containerized-workflow-improvement/</guid><description>Improve Your Containerized Workflow Register for a free and individual session with an expert on how to improve your containerized workflow.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/privacy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy of Container Registry Effective as of: November 1, 2020
Container Registry collects some Personal Data from its Users.
This document can be printed for reference by using the print command in the settings of any browser.
Our Privacy Policy at a Glance This is a condensed overview of the Personal Data we collect for the following purposes and using the following services:
Owner and Data Controller 8gears Ltd.</description></item></channel></rss>