<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Working With Artifacts on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/</link><description>Recent content in Working With Artifacts on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 12:47:27 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Push and Pull Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/push-and-pull-images/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/push-and-pull-images/</guid><description>Push and Pull Images Pushing and pulling images is explained in detail in this getting started guide.</description></item><item><title>Tag Retention</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tag-retention/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tag-retention/</guid><description>Tag Retention As a project administrator, you can save storage capacity by defining rules to govern the number and retention period of artifacts stored in a repository. This allows you to keep only the necessary artifacts and discard those that are no longer required or have been superseded by a newer version. Managing your repository in this way can help ensure that only the most needed artifacts are kept, freeing up valuable storage space.</description></item><item><title>Artifact Page</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/artifact-page/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/artifact-page/</guid><description>Artifact Page When you click on a single artifact, you will be redirected to a view showing detailed information about this artifact. In this view, you can also perform a few additional actions on the selected artifact.
Tags Overview Working with tags is described in detail in another tutorial since the features for doing this are distributed across the GUI. The current section explains general GUI features that are available in the single artifact view.</description></item><item><title>Tag Immutability</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tag-immutability/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/tag-immutability/</guid><description>Tag Immutability What Is Tag Immutability and Why You Need It Harbor, the technology behind Container Registry, cannot (yet) deal with the situation when more than one image has the same tag. When there is an image in the registry with a certain tag, and then another image with the same tag is pushed to it, the first image loses its tag. The second image, pushed later, retains the tag but only until the next image with the same tag is pushed.</description></item><item><title>Working With Tags</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/working-with-tags/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/images/working-with-tags/</guid><description>Working With Tags Image tags have a function similar to those of the branch refs in Git: pointing to a state of the artifact at a specific time. Originally, the purpose of image tags was to differentiate between multiple versions of the same image. But more often than not different tags may refer to the same image.
The tags come in handy when you want to pull and run an image.</description></item></channel></rss>