<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Administration Manual on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/</link><description>Recent content in Administration Manual on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 09:52:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registration for System Admins</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/registration-for-system-admins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/registration-for-system-admins/</guid><description>Registration for System Admins: Create a New Instance All accounts with a Dedicated Service subscription can have multiple users. For the first time, the system administrator must complete the subscription purchase and configure the instance to enable other users to work with it later.
Users of Individual accounts are considered system admins of their accounts. The registration is the same.
To start working with Container Registry:
Go to our pricing page; Select your subscription or start a free trial; Fill in the form and provide your credit card details; Check your emails: you must have received a confirmation that your account has been created; Inside the email, click on password to display your password; you will be re-directed to a single use secure URL generated by OneTimeSecret where you can see your password for the Container Registry account; INFO The password will be kept by OneTimeSecret for a while but try to finish the registration within a few hours.</description></item><item><title>User Management</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/user-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/user-management/</guid><description>User Management Add Another System Admin You can make another user a system admin:
In the navigation pane, expand the Administration section; Select Users; Select a user name from the list; Click SET AS ADMIN. The new admin will have the same rights as the existing ones.
Revoke System Admin Access To revoke admin access rights, repeat the steps from the previous section. Instead of Set as Admin, you will see REVOKE ADMIN after selecting user names.</description></item><item><title>System Robot Accounts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-robot-accounts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-robot-accounts/</guid><description>System Robot Accounts Robot accounts are used to let another application log in to Container Registry automatically.
The overview of all robot accounts in your instance is available from Navigation -&amp;gt; Robot Accounts.
Please note that all robot accounts get a prefix to their names when they are created. By default, the prefix is robot$. It is possible to configure another prefix as described here.
Available Robot Account Permissions Robot accounts can access Container Registry through API or a command line tool but never the GUI.</description></item><item><title>Endpoints For Replications and Proxy Cache</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/endpoints-for-replications-and-proxy-cache/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/endpoints-for-replications-and-proxy-cache/</guid><description>Endpoints For Replications and Proxy Cache Projects Endpoints are container image registries. They can be instances of the Container Registry platform, or other Harbor-based registries, or even non-Harbor-based ones.
Non-Harbor Registries: General Information Supported Non-Harbor Registries For Replications Ali Cloud Container Registry (Alibaba ACR); Artifact Hub; AWS Elastic Container Registry; Azure Container Registry; Docker Hub; Docker registry; DTR; GitHub GHCR; Gitlab; Google Container Registry; Harbor; Huawei SWR; Jfrog Artifactory; Quay; Tencent TCR.</description></item><item><title>System-Wide Labels</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-wide-labels/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-wide-labels/</guid><description>System-Wide Labels Labels are colored tags that can be added to artifacts and are only visible in the Container Registry GUI. They help you to find artifacts quickly since they can be used in some filters and since they are more eye-catchy than tags. They can be added on the project level by project administrators as explained here, but system administrators can also create system-wide labels that can be used for all projects.</description></item><item><title>Project Quotas</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/project-quotas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/project-quotas/</guid><description>Project Quotas Individual accounts have 1 GB of storage included. Dedicated accounts have 100 GB. You can set the upper limit for storage usage for every project.
Overview of the Storage Usage In the Project Quotas tab of the navigation pane, you can check how much storage is used and by which projects. Default disk space per project shows how much storage every newly created project will be assigned. The bar in the Storage column of the overview shows the percentage of storage use.</description></item><item><title>Terminal Deletion of Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/terminal-deletion-of-images/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/terminal-deletion-of-images/</guid><description>Terminal Deletion of Images: Garbage Collection A simple delete operation is not enough to remove images – to be precise, their blob files – from the system. When you use a delete button on the artifacts overview page inside a repository, it simply deletes the corresponding item from the GUI. It means that simple deletion does not clean up your storage, and you may be hitting your project quotas even if you do not see a lot of artifacts in there.</description></item><item><title>Other System Settings</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/other-system-settings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/other-system-settings/</guid><description>Other System Settings Under Administration -&amp;gt; Configuration -&amp;gt; System Settings you will find a few more system-wide settings. Project Authorship In the dropdown Project Creation, you can specify who can create new projects in your instance. You have a choice between system admins and all other users.
Token Expiration You need a token every time you want to login into your private registry from Docker. You can specify how many minutes it is valid.</description></item><item><title>Proxy Cache Projects</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/proxy-cache-projects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/proxy-cache-projects/</guid><description>Proxy Cache Projects Why Use Container Registry as a Proxy Cache Container Registry can be used as a proxy cache for images originally stored on Docker Hub.
There are a few reasons why you would avoid pulling images from Docker Hub directly.
Docker Rate Limit Docker Hub has a download limit rate which is defined differently for different subscription plans. In our blog post, we explain why you can hit the limits quite quickly and which consequences it may have for your workflows.</description></item></channel></rss>