<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Administration Manual on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/</link><description>Recent content in Administration Manual on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Registration for System Admins</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/registration-for-system-admins/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/registration-for-system-admins/</guid><description>Registration for System Admins: Create a New Instance All accounts with a Dedicated Service subscription can have multiple users. For the first time, the system administrator must complete the subscription purchase and configure the instance to enable other users to work with it later.
Users of Individual accounts are considered system admins of their accounts. The registration is the same.
To start working with Container Registry:
Go to our pricing page; Select your subscription or start a free trial; Fill in the form and provide your credit card details; Check your emails: you must have received a confirmation that your account has been created; Inside the email, click on password to display your password; you will be re-directed to a single use secure URL generated by OneTimeSecret where you can see your password for the Container Registry account; NOTE</description></item><item><title>User Management</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/user-management/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/user-management/</guid><description>User Management Add Another System Admin You can make another user a system admin:
In the navigation pane, expand the Administration section; Select Users; Select a user name from the list; Click SET AS ADMIN. The new admin will have the same rights as the existing ones.
Revoke System Admin Access To revoke admin access rights, repeat the steps from the previous section. Instead of Set as Admin, you will see REVOKE ADMIN after selecting user names.</description></item><item><title>System Robot Accounts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-robot-accounts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/system-robot-accounts/</guid><description>System Robot Accounts The procedure is similar to creating robot accounts on the project level as described here with the difference that, as a system admin, you can create robots that have access to multiple projects.
To create a system robot account:
Go to the Administration tab; Select Robot Accounts; Click Create New Robot Account; Fill in the form: Give your robot a catchy name; Select if it should expire and how soon from the dropdown; Optionally, add a description; Set which projects it should have access to: Select Cover all projects and set permissions that apply to all projects.</description></item></channel></rss>