<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configure User Authentication on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/</link><description>Recent content in Configure User Authentication on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 09:52:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Database Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/database-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/database-authentication/</guid><description>Database Authentication The database user authnetication mode is applied by default. With this mode, all user management happens in the Container Registry GUI and the data is stored in the local database.
When selecting this authentication mode, keep in mind that once you added any users (except for yourself) to the instance using the database mode, the instance will be locked from switching to any other mode.
Nonetheless, this mode has a few advantages.</description></item><item><title>UAA Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/uaa-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/uaa-authentication/</guid><description>UAA Authentication A user authentication and authorization server issues access tokens for your application to make it able to access another application: in this case, your Container Registry instance. You can configure a UAA server by yourself or select a provider that will set up for you a UAA instance. This instance will generate a token every time the user identity was confirmed – the user was authenticated – to enable user authorization that allows the user to perform certain actions in the system he was successfully logged in to.</description></item><item><title>LDAP/AD Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/ldap-ad-authentication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/ldap-ad-authentication/</guid><description>LDAP/AD Authentication Every company needs a directory where all user login data is kept. There are two popular technologies for configuring and managing such directories – Windows Active Directory (AD) and Lightweight Directory Access Protocol – that are Harbor-compatible. It means that you can use an LDAP/AD server to add new users to the Container Registry instance and manage existing accounts on the server.
Indeed, you need to set up and configure such a server before you can activate this kind of user authentication in Container Registry.</description></item><item><title>OIDC Authentication</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/oidc-authentication/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/authentication/oidc-authentication/</guid><description>OpenID Connect Single Sign-On Authentication We support all OIDC compliant identity providers. In the User Guides section, you can find selected configuration tutorials that explain how the settings look like on the provider side.
This reference, explains what you need to do in your Container Registry instance to enable and configure the OIDC login. Usually, you should proceed with this tutorial if you have access to your OIDC&amp;rsquo;s provider management console to set up new client.</description></item></channel></rss>