<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project Configuration on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/</link><description>Recent content in Project Configuration on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 12:16:21 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Robot Accounts</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/robot-accounts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/robot-accounts/</guid><description>Robot Accounts Robot accounts are used to access your project through an API. They perform a limited range of actions that you can specify per account and are generally used for workflow, deployment, and testing automation. Robot accounts created on the project level can access only one project. They cannot be transferred to other projects.
To create robots that have access to multiple projects, create system robot accounts as explained here.</description></item><item><title>Webhooks</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/webhooks/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/projects/configuration/webhooks/</guid><description>Webhooks Webhooks are API push notifications sent in the form of HTTP or HHTPS POST requests. They pro-actively deliver messages to other applications when some event occurs inside their own application.
They can inform or trigger further events in the destination application. For instance, you can directly deploy an application upon the image push. This allows you to automate your deployments.
In Container Registry, you can add either an HTTP or Slack-based HTTPS URL that will be used for receiving the messages by the target application.</description></item></channel></rss>