<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started Guide on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started Guide on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:51:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prerequisites</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/prerequisites/</guid><description>Prerequisites The only prerequisite for you to get started is to use an OCI compliant container runtime environment, such as Docker or Podman.
Check the system and hardware requirements for Docker in its official documentation and follow the instructions to get it running on your machine. You can refer to the respective install guide for Podman.</description></item><item><title>New User Sign Up</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/new-user-sign-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/new-user-sign-up/</guid><description>New User Sign Up Container Registry is a cloud-based solution that you can use in your browser or CLI tool or through an API.
Your Instance on Container Registry All accounts with a Dedicated Service subscription receive a subdomain on container-registry.com. Your organization can also request a custom domain.
Every subdomain/domain represents one instance. For different instances, you need different login credentials.
Registration Methods As a user, you can use one of these methods to register in your Container Registry instance:</description></item><item><title>Working With Helm Charts and OCI Registries</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/working-with-helm-charts-and-oci-registries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/working-with-helm-charts-and-oci-registries/</guid><description>Working With OCI Helm Charts Harbor stopped offering ChartMuseum interfaces to store Helm Charts. As of now, only OCI registry interfaces are used to store Helm Charts. Interacting with Helm Charts stored in OCI registries is different, but it has some advantages over the old Chart Museum.
With OCI based Helm Charts, you get the familiar command syntax as with interacting with container images runtimes. registry login .... The only difference is that you need to use the helm command instead of docker or Podman.</description></item><item><title>Push and Pull Images</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/push-and-pull-images/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/push-and-pull-images/</guid><description>Push and Pull Images Log In to Your Private Registry If you use a private registry, you need to use Docker login to push and pull images to and from Container Registry. For this, you can use your Container Registry username but you need to generate your CLI login for Docker first.
Go to your user profile in the upper right corner of the cockpit: Copy the CLI secret: In your command line tool, log in to Docker: docker login your-subdomain.</description></item><item><title>Other Useful Features</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/other-useful-features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/getting-started-guide/other-useful-features/</guid><description>Other Useful Features Our Harbor-based cloud service allows you to manage your images easier. Apart from pulling and pushing images to and from your container registry, you can:
Facilitate your Kubernetes deployments by seamless integration between your Kubernetes clusters and Harbor-based container registries; using Kubernetes YAML manifests: Helm Charts; access your Chart Museum directly from the GUI Bypass connectivity issues by using a proxy cache: a pull-through cache for another target registry; a cached copy is checked against the target and is always up-to-date.</description></item></channel></rss>