<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>User Manual on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/</link><description>Recent content in User Manual on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:36:41 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why Use Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/why-use-container-registry/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/why-use-container-registry/</guid><description>Why Use Container Registry as a Service Container registries are storages for your container images. It is an essential service for containerization technology that saves you a lot of headaches when you run Kubernetes clusters to test and deploy your containerized applications.
Why Use a Container Registry When you work with Kubernetes deployments, you face the chicken-egg dilemma: you cannot keep the images in the cluster but you need them to run it.</description></item><item><title>What Is Harbor?</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/what-is-harbor/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/what-is-harbor/</guid><description>What Is Harbor? Our service is built upon Harbor. Harbor is an open-source technology for storing and managing container images. It was developed by VMware, a leading provider of virtual machines, and then transferred to the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), one of the biggest open-source initiatives.
In its turn, the Harbor project evolved out of Docker&amp;rsquo;s source code. Its contributors attempted to enhance the latter and eliminate its security problems.</description></item><item><title>Container Registry User Interface: A Short Overview</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/container-registry-user-interface-a-short-overview/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 12:11:51 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/container-registry-user-interface-a-short-overview/</guid><description>Container Registry User Interface: A Short Overview When you log in to your Container Registry account as a user, you will see the following console.
INFO If you log in as an administrator, you will see an additional administration section. Refer to our Administration Guide for the GUI features overview.
Main GUI Features The navigation pane provides you access to your projects and logs.
Projects are folders for your images which can be assigned certain settings.</description></item><item><title>Working With Logs</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/working-with-logs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/working-with-logs/</guid><description>Working With Logs Logs track everything that happens in your system. You can access logs from different places in the GUI.
Event Logs You will see this side bar on the right from everywhere in Container Registry. Hover over the EVENT LOG tab to exapnd it.
Event log includes high-level events, for instance, adding or deleting a new user to the system:
In some cases, project-related events will be also displayed in this section.</description></item><item><title>Dedicated vs Individual Account</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/dedicated-vs-individual-account/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/dedicated-vs-individual-account/</guid><description>Dedicated vs Individual Account Container Registry offers three types of pricing plans:
individual; dedicated; custom/enterprise. The present documentation is mostly written with dedicated accounts in mind. We would like to explain the differences between the three. The table below summarizes critical distinctions. You can also refer to our pricing page.
Position Individual Dedicated Custom Tenants 1 tenant Multitenancy Multitenancy Repositores Only private Private and public Private and public Domain c8n.io Subdomain on container-registry.</description></item><item><title>Double-Starred Patterns</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/double-starred-patterns/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/user-manual/double-starred-patterns/</guid><description>Double-Starred Patterns Some Container Registry GUI features allow you to use string matching instead of entering complete names of repositories or tags. That comes in handy if you create separate repositories or tags for every stage in the software development lifecycle and follow a naming convention. In this case, you can select more than one repository or tag by typing in only the pattern once instead of listing all their names.</description></item></channel></rss>