<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Configure Artifacts Replication on Container Registry</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/replication/</link><description>Recent content in Configure Artifacts Replication on Container Registry</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 09:52:03 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/replication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configure Replication Rules</title><link>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/replication/configure-replication-rules/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://container-registry.com/docs/administration-manual/replication/configure-replication-rules/</guid><description>Configure Replication Rules Replication rules specify which artifacts will be moved between registries and how they should be moved. Each replication rule includes:
a filter to catch particular artifacts; a scheduler; a flattening rule. Create or Configure a Replication Rule Prerequisite You need at least one endpoint – a registry to push or pull images from – to create a new replication rule.
Steps In the navigation, select Administration and then Replications; Click + New Replication Rule; If you want to edit an existing one, select it for editing as explained below; Fill in the form: Name should not have any white spaces; Description is optional; Replication mode: Push-based means that you will push images from your current Container Registry instance into a remote one; Pull-based means that you will pull images to your current Container registry instance from a remote one; Resource filter: in the push replication mode, your current instance is the resource, whereas, in the pull mode, the resource is the remote registry; the resource filter selects which artifacts should be included in the replication: Name is the repository name; however, you can include all repositories by specifying in this field only the name of the project or using patterns; Tag is the artifact tag; Label; In the Resource dropdown, you can choose between the artifact type: chart, image, or any artifact.</description></item></channel></rss>